
        

var all_qa = {
    "0": {
        "question": "jake\u2019s been trying to build brand awareness for his new clothing line. initial branding attempts were successful, but he now wants to scale things to a larger degree. jake can reach a wide audience by using smart display campaigns. how many websites and apps are available for smart display campaigns to run across?",
        "answer": ["3,000,000"]
    },
    "1": {
        "question": "robert manages a website that sells sporting goods. he wants his products to be featured in various online sporting publications while potential customers are researching and comparing different football brands online. which option will help robert influence customer consideration?",
        "answer": ["in-market audiences"]
    },
    "2": {
        "question": "alan has introduced a new line of scooters on his website and is using a google display ad campaign to promote them. he selects \u201cbuild awareness\u201d as the marketing objective for his campaign. why would alan choose \u201cbuild awareness\u201d as his marketing objective?",
        "answer": ["to <a>reach a broad audience for his scooters</a>."]
    },
    "3": {
        "question": "which two statements are true about how you can use targeting options to optimize a google ads campaign?",
        "answer": ["device targeting allows you to reach customers on any device: desktops, tablets, andsmartphones.", "location targeting allows your ads to be served only in the specific geographiclocations you choose."]
    },
    "4": {
        "question": "what are two reasons a marketer might use responsive display ads?",
        "answer": ["extended reach: create ads that serve in most ad slot sizes, into both native and non-native inventory.", "cost-effective: get more conversions at a similar cost-per-acquisition."]
    },
    "5": {
        "question": "when should you use amphtml ads?",
        "answer": ["when your goal is to provide safer ad experiences.", "when your goal is to provide faster ad experiences."]
    },
    "6": {
        "question": "josephine is in the process of creating ads within her standard display campaign. she finds that there are two main ad formats that she can leverage. what are the two main ad formats used in a standard display campaign?",
        "answer": ["uploaded ads (image &amp; amphtml)", "responsive display ads"]
    },
    "7": {
        "question": "mike recently started using google display ads to create a more automated approach to managing his campaigns. what\u2019s one automation model that smart display campaigns provides that might help mike?",
        "answer": ["automated targeting"]
    },
    "8": {
        "question": "what\u2019s a key benefit of responsive display ads?",
        "answer": ["they automatically create ads that serve all ad slot sizes.", "you can upload your own creative assets."]
    },
    "9": {
        "question": "zoe runs a sports media website that caters to fans of many different types of sports. she\u2019s starting a google display ads campaign and is considering methods to reach her sports-loving audience. what\u2019s a compelling reason for zoe to use affinity audiences?",
        "answer": ["affinity audiences allow her to reach sports enthusiasts."]
    },
    "10": {
        "question": "how does google display ads drive marketing results every day for thousands of advertisers around the world?",
        "answer": ["it allows them to run ads and connect with audiences through gmail, youtube, and millions of other websites."]
    },
    "11": {
        "question": "brian owns a company that makes inexpensive replacement parts for bicycles. he\u2019s ready to increase the scale of his business and wants to use google display ads to drive sales. which feature of a google display ads will help brian achieve his business objectives?",
        "answer": ["his ads can appear on websites relevant to bicycles, and therefore connect him to his potential audience."]
    },
    "12": {
        "question": "your company wants to have greater success online. what are two ways that google ads can drive your business goals?",
        "answer": ["boost your conversions by connecting you to people in the moments that matter.", "help you reach a wider audience and maximize exposure."]
    },
    "13": {
        "question": "what is a key benefit of smart display campaigns?",
        "answer": ["a smart display campaign can be created with minimal input from advertisers."]
    },
    "14": {
        "question": "phillip wants to create a new google display ad campaign and base his targeting on an existing remarketing list named checkout abandoners. how can the similar audiences targeting option help phillip achieve his marketing goals?",
        "answer": ["similar audiences will find users who are similar to those on the checkout abandonerslist."]
    },
    "15": {
        "question": "match the marketers with the display ad format that fits them best. (formats can be used more than once.)",
        "answer": ["responsive display ads", "amphtml ads", "responsive display ads", "image ads", "none"]
    },
    "16": {
        "question": "trevor has discounted an entire line of products on his website and wants to use google display ads to drive sales. how does google display ads targeting help trevor reach his marketing objective?",
        "answer": ["google display ads will help place trevor\u2019s ad before customers who already showed interest in his brand."]
    },
    "17": {
        "question": "as a marketing director at a large company, cara\u2019s considering launching a google display ads campaign, as it will let her reach global internet users across as many websites and apps as possible. what\u2019s another benefit a google display ads campaign will provide cara?",
        "answer": ["it makes it possible for her to engage with valuable audiences quickly and often."]
    },
    "18": {
        "question": "amanda uses \u201cinfluence consideration\u201d as a marketing objective for her google display ads campaign. which targeting options are a good fit for amanda\u2019s campaign?",
        "answer": ["in-market audiences, custom intent audiences, similar audiences"]
    },
    "19": {
        "question": "which statement is true about the value of google display ads?",
        "answer": ["it uses best-in-class automation and bidding to reach millions of users at just the right moment."]
    },
    "20": {
        "question": "olivia manages an online store that sells musical instruments. she\u2019ll soon host a jazz event and wants to create awareness around it, especially within the community of jazz enthusiasts. which targeting option should olivia choose in order to achieve her marketing goal?",
        "answer": ["affinity audiences"]
    },
    "21": {
        "question": "marie is a marketer trying to maximize specific user actions after the click. which automated bidding strategy should she use to accomplish this?",
        "answer": ["conversion-focused bidding"]
    },
    "22": {
        "question": "when deciding between responsive display ads and uploaded ads, when would you opt for control rather than for efficiency?",
        "answer": ["when your ads must meet exact branding requirements."]
    },
    "23": {
        "question": "joshua has an online store that sells skateboard equipment. he notices that potential customers are looking at specific skateboards but leaving his website without completing a purchase. which google display campaign option can joshua use to feature the same skateboards viewed to potential customers who didn\u2019t complete a purchase?",
        "answer": ["dynamic remarketing"]
    },
    "24": {
        "question": "adam has determined that \u201cdrive action\u201d is the appropriate marketing objective for his new display campaign. what are two relevant options he might use to reach his goal? (choose two.) select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["standard remarketing", "dynamic remarketing"]
    },
    "25": {
        "question": "a marketer is keeping track of the revenue generated by his campaigns. he wants to get a specific return for his ad spend. which type of automated bidding strategy will meet his needs?",
        "answer": ["a revenue-focused bidding strategy"]
    },
    "26": {
        "question": "gavin is creating a google display ads campaign designed to drive sales on his website. he wants to reach potential customers who viewed pages on his website and entice them to make purchases with a discount code. which option will best serve gavin\u2019s marketing goals?",
        "answer": ["remarketing"]
    },
    "27": {
        "question": "what\u2019s an advantage of using responsive display ads?",
        "answer": ["they will automatically create ads from your images, videos, headlines, logos, and descriptions."]
    },
    "28": {
        "question": "which display ad format runs in both native and non-native inventory?",
        "answer": ["responsive display ads"]
    },
    "29": {
        "question": "in order to drive sales with her google display ads campaign, charlotte wants to reach audiences who looked at products on her website, with new ads for those exact products. which targeting option should she choose to help achieve that goal?",
        "answer": ["dynamic remarketing"]
    },
    "30": {
        "question": "what are two benefits of automated bidding? (choose two.) select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["time saving", "cross analysis"]
    },
    "31": {
        "question": "what\u2019s one reason to use a responsive display ad for your campaign?",
        "answer": ["you want to increase ad performance."]
    },
    "32": {
        "question": "brian\u2019s desired audience isn\u2019t covered by the segments in-market audiences offers. what\u2019s another suitable option brian could choose to help him influence potential customer consideration?",
        "answer": ["custom intent audiences"]
    },
    "33": {
        "question": "which factors should an advertiser consider when deciding on a bidding strategy?",
        "answer": ["user journey complexities, performance, and auctions"]
    },
    "34": {
        "question": "thelma is the marketing director for an online toy store. she\u2019s creating a display campaign to reach parents between the ages of 25 to 34. which targeting option should thelma select to achieve her marketing goal?",
        "answer": ["demographic targeting"]
    },
    "35": {
        "question": "mandy has a large art-supply company that sells through both her brick-and-mortar store and online. she wants to increase the awareness of her brand and drive higher sales. how can google display ads help mandy achieve her business objectives?",
        "answer": ["it places mandy\u2019s ads against the most relevant content by using best-in-class intent signals. "]
    },
    "36": {
        "question": "how does google display ads drive results every day for thousands of advertisers?",
        "answer": ["its real-time view of context and behavior across the web powers unique understandings ofintent."]
    },
    "37": {
        "question": "what are two ways google ads can fuel your business goals? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["get more of the right people to visit your website.", "increase online, in-app, in-person, and over-the-phone sales."]
    },
    "38": {
        "question": "what\u2019s one benefit of using responsive display ads?",
        "answer": ["they can run on native inventory."]
    },
    "39": {
        "question": "steve wants to use google display ads to reach new customers who are looking to purchase products similar to his. which audience type should steve try to reach to meet his marketing goal?",
        "answer": ["in-market audiences"]
    },
    "40": {
        "question": "amanda is the marketing manager for a plant nursery. she has a large number of campaigns and needs help keeping her bids relevant every day. how can automated bidding help her?",
        "answer": ["by setting her bids when auctions happen."]
    },
    "41": {
        "question": "why does automating your bid versus using manual bidding contribute to a successful google ads campaign?",
        "answer": ["if you do not bid efficiently, you could miss valuable conversions."]
    },
    "42": {
        "question": "mary feels confident managing google search campaigns and is interested in extending her marketing reach with the help of google display ads. she\u2019s trying to decide whether to create a standard display campaign or a smart display campaign. why would mary choose standard display campaigns over smart display campaigns?",
        "answer": ["she wants full control over all aspects of her display campaigns."]
    },
    "43": {
        "question": "darren notices that many people viewed specific products on his website without purchasing them. he creates a google display ad to drive sales of those exact products. which option will best suit darren\u2019s marketing goal?",
        "answer": ["dynamic remarketing"]
    },
    "44": {
        "question": "which display ad format should you use if you\u2019re concerned about malware and want a secure ad experience across platforms?",
        "answer": ["amphtml ads"]
    },
    "45": {
        "question": "loretta is the advertising director for a large meal-kit company. she\u2019s setting up a google display campaign to identify and engage with large audiences in order to extend their market reach. which statement most accurately describes the reach a google display campaign can provide loretta?",
        "answer": ["it allows her to reach over 90% of global internet users across millions of appsand websites."]
    },
    "46": {
        "question": "cassandra wants to customize her google display ads based on how potential customers previously engaged with her website. which option best suits her needs?",
        "answer": ["remarketing"]
    },
    "47": {
        "question": "amy has created a new brand for her company\u2019s goldfish training materials. she knows that other companies train goldfish and it is a popular sport, but realizes that it is a niche market. she wants to use a google display ads campaign to build awareness for her new brand. which google display ad targeting option can help amy with her goal of creating awareness within her niche market?",
        "answer": ["custom affinity audiences"]
    },
    "48": {
        "question": "lucy is creating a new display campaign with the goal of building awareness. which two targeting options might be suitable for her to use? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["affinity audiences", "demographic targeting"]
    },
    "49": {
        "question": "how does google display ads drive marketing results for thousands of advertisers worldwide?",
        "answer": ["it harnesses best-in-class signals to place ads against the most relevant content."]
    },
    "50": {
        "question": "karen owns a large online business selling antiques. she wants to create a smart display campaign. what are two of the three inputs she must supply in order to create a smart display campaign? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["budget amount", "creative assets"]
    },
    "51": {
        "question": "which display ad format automatically creates ads from uploaded headlines, logos, images, and videos?",
        "answer": ["responsive display ads"]
    },
    "52": {
        "question": "google ads offers a variety of campaign types which determine where your ad will appear and the format in which it will be displayed. what are the available campaign types?",
        "answer": ["search, display, video, shopping, and app"]
    },
    "53": {
        "question": "which statement accurately describes the reach of affinity audiences\u2019 targeting?",
        "answer": ["it reaches tv-like audiences, based on their lifestyles, interests, and passions."]
    },
    "54": {
        "question": "frank runs a scuba-diving business that offers lessons and sells scuba-diving equipment. frank wants to engage with users who are researching scuba-diving lessons. which marketing objective should frank choose when creating his display campaign?",
        "answer": ["influence consideration"]
    },
    "55": {
        "question": "karen has opened a new business and is using google display ads to build awareness of her new products. how does google display ads targeting help karen reach her marketing objective?",
        "answer": ["by getting her ad in front of the right people, in the right place, at the right time."]
    },
    "56": {
        "question": "julie wants to show potential customers products they previously viewed on her website. what does julie need in place to create dynamically generated display ads within a dynamic remarketing campaign?",
        "answer": ["a pre-uploaded feed"]
    },
    "57": {
        "question": "felix wants to start showing his google display ads to a narrower audience with the help of demographic targeting. which two types of data are included in demographic targeting? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["age", "gender"]
    },
    "58": {
        "question": "when a responsive display ad is automatically assembled, what\u2019s adjusted to fit the ad slot?",
        "answer": ["size, appearance, and format"]
    },
    "59": {
        "question": "viktor\u2019s been tracking the conversions in his display campaign for the last 30 days. he\u2019s had 24 conversions over that time, and plans to use target return on ad spend (roas) as his automated bidding strategy. which type of automated bidding strategy will viktor be using?",
        "answer": ["revenue-focused bidding "]
    },
    "60": {
        "question": "what can automated bidding help an advertiser improve",
        "answer": ["performance"]
    },
    "61": {
        "question": "kim is seeing significant performance from her google display remarketing campaign, and wants to expand upon it. which targeting option should she choose to accomplish this?",
        "answer": ["similar audiences"]
    },
    "62": {
        "question": "which group would you be able to reach with a google display campaign using demographic targeting?",
        "answer": ["27-year-old men"]
    },
    "63": {
        "question": "what\u2019s an advantage of the reach of responsive display ads?",
        "answer": ["they automatically adjust your creative asset\u2019s size, appearance, and format to fit just aboutany native or non-native ad slot."]
    },
    "64": {
        "question": "you choose influence consideration as your marketing objective and the similar audiences targeting option for a google display ad campaign. in google display ad campaigns, what are similar audiences built from?",
        "answer": ["remarketing lists"]
    },
    "65": {
        "question": "colin is planning out a new google display ads campaign with the \u201cbuild awareness\u201d marketing objective in mind. why would colin choose \u201cbuild awareness\u201d as his marketing objective?",
        "answer": ["he wants to get his display ads in front of as many people as possible."]
    },
    "66": {
        "question": "your company provides home maintenance services and you want to reach more potential customers. you have a limited budget to work with. why is google ads right for you?",
        "answer": ["you can set your own budget and can change it at any time."]
    },
    "67": {
        "question": "kevin is determining which google display ads format to use, and choosing between efficiency and control. match the ad he\u2019s creating to the appropriate ad format option.",
        "answer": ["efficiency (1)", "control (2)"]
    },
    "68": {
        "question": "the customer journey has become more complex, requiring a dedicated bidding strategy. google\u2019s solution is automated bidding. how can automated bidding benefit advertisers?",
        "answer": ["is auction-specific to increase the chance for conversion.", "uses machine learning to set bids, which saves time."]
    },
    "69": {
        "question": "simon\u2019s using a google smart display campaign to build out his ads. what benefit do google smart display campaigns give simon?",
        "answer": ["his ads are automatically generated from the building blocks he provides, like headlines,descriptions, logos, and images."]
    },
    "70": {
        "question": "how does google display ads help advertisers meet their marketing objectives and drive results?",
        "answer": ["by helping advertisers deliver relevant advertising as people browse the web."]
    },
    "71": {
        "question": "what\u2019s an advantage of responsive display ads?",
        "answer": ["they\u2019re built for performance, reach, and scale."]
    },
    "72": {
        "question": "what\u2019s provided by responsive display ads?",
        "answer": ["reach, simplicity, automation"]
    },
    "73": {
        "question": "susan doesn\u2019t have time to create display ads herself. she hopes to use a smart display campaign to automatically generate ads. which two building blocks must susan supply in order for a smart display campaign to automate her ad creation? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["headlines", "images"]
    },
    "74": {
        "question": "what are two examples of the types of audiences you could reach when using affinity audiences as a targeting option? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["golf enthusiasts", "tv comedy fans"]
    },
    "75": {
        "question": "catherine received a significant amount of traffic to her online pet store after launching her display campaign. unfortunately, many visitors to her online store didn\u2019t make a purchase. when creating a new display campaign, which marketing objective should catherine choose in order to reengage with these visitors?",
        "answer": ["drive action"]
    },
    "76": {
        "question": "match each business objective with the google ads campaign type that best meets it. (each campaign type can be used only once.)",
        "answer": ["shopping campaign", "appcampaign", "display campaign"]
    },
    "77": {
        "question": "paul\u2019s interested in generating conversions with google display ads, but he\u2019s not confident in setting bids himself. he\u2019s relying on smart display campaigns to help. which two bidding strategies used in smart display campaigns can paul choose from to automatically set his bids? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["target cpa (cost per acquisition)", "target roas (return on ad spend)"]
    },
    "78": {
        "question": "bill wants to reach valuable, relevant audiences and engage with them quickly and often with his ads. how will creating a display ads campaign allow him to reach his goal?",
        "answer": ["it allows him to reach over 90% of global internet users across more than three million appsand websites."]
    },
    "79": {
        "question": "ben sells housewares through his website and app. what are two ways that google ads can fuel his business goals and help him achieve his objectives? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["increase overall installs and interactions with his app.", "help users find and discover his products."]
    },
    "80": {
        "question": "when should you use responsive display ads?",
        "answer": ["when your primary goal is performance."]
    },
    "81": {
        "question": "howard\u2019s in the process of creating a google display campaign and decides to use custom intent audiences as a targeting option. he\u2019d like to influence customer consideration, but his niche audience isn\u2019t covered by an in-market audience segment. which two data inputs can howard submit to best represent his audience? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["keywords", "urls"]
    },
    "82": {
        "question": "jasmine is the director of marketing for a chain of clothing stores. she has been given a set budget and needs to drive as many potential customers to her website as possible. which automated bidding strategy should she use in her campaign?",
        "answer": ["maximize clicks"]
    },
    "83": {
        "question": "doreen is looking to drive sales on her website, and is considering creating a google display remarketing campaign how might remarketing help her meet her marketing objective?",
        "answer": ["it reaches audiences who previously visited her website as they browse networkwebsites anduse network apps."]
    },
    "84": {
        "question": "gloria owns a surfing clothing line. she wants to increase the awareness of her brand and drive higher sales. how can google display ads help gloria achieve her business objective?",
        "answer": ["it harnesses best-in-class intent signals to place her ads against the most relevant content."]
    },
    "85": {
        "question": "quinn recently launched a display campaign for his women\u2019s clothing store. since the launch, his website traffic has increased, but sales have remained flat. which story shows quinn using remarketing to drive action?",
        "answer": ["quinn creates a list of cart abandoners that identifies users who visited his website,considered buying his clothing, but didn\u2019t purchase. he shows them an ad with a promotionaldiscount code."]
    },
    "86": {
        "question": "nathan manages a website that sells bicycles. he\u2019s using a google ads display campaign to drive purchases in that segment, and chooses in-market audiences as his targeting option. what\u2019s the advantage in-market audiences gives nathan in reaching his marketing goals?",
        "answer": ["connects him with audiences most interested in what he has to offer."]
    },
    "87": {
        "question": "ken sees a high level of success from his display campaigns, and wants to take performance to the next level with the help of dynamic remarketing. how can dynamic remarketing benefit him?",
        "answer": ["it will show exact products to potential customers that have previously seen them on hiswebsite."]
    },
    "88": {
        "question": "a company creates niche sporting equipment for active female senior citizens. the company expects potential customers to be above 65 years old, either with or without a shown interest in sports. the company\u2019s marketing team is looking to build awareness about their company\u2019s innovative products. which option can best help them reach their specific audience?",
        "answer": ["demographic targeting"]
    },
    "89": {
        "question": "which two are available in google ads? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["device targeting, which allows you to serve your ads to users on desktops, smartphones, andtablets.", "language targeting, which lets you reach people with your selected language as theirbrowser\u2019s language setting."]
    },
    "90": {
        "question": "which type of automated bidding strategy is target return on ad spend (roas)?",
        "answer": ["revenue-focused bidding"]
    },
    "91": {
        "question": "claire has created a google display remarketing campaign. what\u2019s the most likely reason she decided on remarketing?",
        "answer": ["drive action "]
    },
    "92": {
        "question": "sierra owns a small business and handles many responsibilities, from logistics to marketing. she\u2019s seen a lot of success with google search (hundreds of conversions a month) and would like to increase her reach by creating a display campaign. but she\u2019d like it to be as effortless as possible. what type of display campaign should she run?",
        "answer": ["a smart display campaign"]
    },
    "93": {
        "question": "diana is running a successful remarketing campaign. she wants to expand her reach with other targeting options. while creating a new google ads display campaign with the \u201cinfluence consideration\u201d marketing objective, she chooses similar audiences as her targeting option. what information is used to identify similar audiences?",
        "answer": ["audience interest around different topics"]
    },
    "94": {
        "question": "google display ads lets advertisers upload their own creative assets to the system. this allows advertisers greater control over the look and feel of their ads. what are the two types of uploaded ads?",
        "answer": ["image ads and amphtml ads"]
    },
    "95": {
        "question": "angela\u2019s ready to get started with her first smart display campaign, but her account isn\u2019t yet eligible due to not having enough conversions in the last 30 days. what\u2019s the minimum number of conversions needed (in the last 30 days) to be eligible to set up a smart display campaign?",
        "answer": ["at least 50 conversions on display or at least 100 conversions on search."]
    },
    "96": {
        "question": "emmy is the marketing director of a large marketing team, looking to reach an audience at scale through smart display campaigns. how might smart display campaign reporting help emmy?",
        "answer": ["in addition to standard google ads reporting, it provides reports that facilitate broad,strategic ad management."]
    },
    "97": {
        "question": "which display ad format adjusts to available ad space?",
        "answer": ["responsive display ads"]
    },
    "98": {
        "question": "bill has released a new line of products for his business and is using google display ads to influence customer consideration. how does google display ads targeting help bill reach his marketing objective?",
        "answer": ["by allowing bill to strategically show his message to users when they\u2019re actively browsing,researching, or comparing the types of products he sells."]
    },
    "99": {
        "question": "what are key factors to keep in mind when choosing a bidding strategy for your campaign?",
        "answer": ["performance, auctions, and user journey complexities"]
    },
    "100": {
        "question": "a small marketing group uses google display ads to help deliver relevant advertising to people browsing the web. which statement is true about where google display ads connects with these valuable audiences?",
        "answer": ["google display ads connects with audiences through gmail, youtube, and millions of otherwebsites partnering with google."]
    },
    "101": {
        "question": "what does a responsive display ad use in its machine-learning model to determine the optimal combination of assets for your ad slot?",
        "answer": ["predictions built from your performance history."]
    },
    "102": {
        "question": "which statement is true about responsive display ads?",
        "answer": ["the ads adjust to available screen space when delivered."]
    },
    "103": {
        "question": "what\u2019s a characteristic of responsive display ads?",
        "answer": ["they let you create ads that serve in all ad slot sizes."]
    },
    "104": {
        "question": "lauren has chosen \u201cinfluence consideration\u201d as the marketing objective in her google display ads campaign. which two targeting options are a good fit for lauren\u2019s campaign? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["similar audiences", "custom intent audiences"]
    },
    "105": {
        "question": "what\u2019s a key benefit of bumper ads?",
        "answer": ["high audience attention"]
    },
    "106": {
        "question": "jasmine\u2019s client is interested in adding youtube to their online marketing strategy. they\u2019d like a first-party data audience solution that lets them find new customers who share characteristics with their existing ones. what would be the ideal first-party data audience solution for this client?",
        "answer": ["similar audiences"]
    },
    "107": {
        "question": "which statement is true about non-skippable in-stream ads?",
        "answer": ["non-skippable in-stream ads complement tv campaigns and incremental reach./non-skippable in-stream ads are available in auction or as a reservation buy."]
    },
    "108": {
        "question": "which statement is true about bumper ads?",
        "answer": []
    },
    "109": {
        "question": "what\u2019s a key benefit of trueview in-stream?",
        "answer": ["it optimizes for impressions instead of views."]
    },
    "110": {
        "question": "arturo has explained to a client who sells electronics that youtube\u2019s detailed demographic audiences can impact their advertising efforts. he knows detailed demographics help advertisers reach audiences based on quantifiable characteristics that matter to the client. what are two of these quantifiable characteristics? (choose two.) select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["homeownership status", "household income"]
    },
    "111": {
        "question": "following the abcd framework, what\u2019s one way to attract viewers and give them a reason to watch an ad?",
        "answer": ["front-load the story arc by opening the ad with impact and grabbing their attention."]
    },
    "112": {
        "question": "which storytelling methods does google recommend for use within your youtube campaigns?",
        "answer": ["tease/amplify/echo, direct shot, the follow-up"]
    },
    "113": {
        "question": "as a youtube creator, kieran can reach over two billion active users each month and use platform innovations to generate content that meets users\u2019 needs. youtube gives him the freedom to express himself, find new opportunities, and make a living while he does it. how does youtube help creators earn a living?",
        "answer": ["creators are paid for sharing ads alongside their content."]
    },
    "114": {
        "question": "google video partners are partnerships formed through which ad service?",
        "answer": ["google adsense"]
    },
    "115": {
        "question": "based on google\u2019s abcds of designing ads for youtube, what are two ways google recommends you connect with your viewers? (choose two.) select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["use humor to boost ad recall, brand awareness, and viewership.", "break the fourth wall in your ad by speaking directly to viewers."]
    },
    "116": {
        "question": "janice\u2019s advertising agency landed a client who\u2019d like to understand how media consumption habits have evolved, prior to spending their budget on youtube. they\u2019re mobile-focused and would like to know the percentage of youtube watch-time that takes place on mobile devices. what percentage of youtube watch-time is on mobile devices?",
        "answer": ["60% of youtube watch-time happens on mobile devices."]
    },
    "117": {
        "question": "drew has a client who\u2019s wavering on whether or not to add youtube to their online advertising strategy. which benefits of youtube audience solutions should drew present for his client\u2019s consideration?",
        "answer": ["real-time data, powerful signals, and cross-device reach"]
    },
    "118": {
        "question": "using custom intent audiences allows brands to drive action on youtube. what\u2019s the key functionality of custom intent audiences?",
        "answer": ["custom intent audiences reach users who recently searched on google."]
    },
    "119": {
        "question": "which elements are used to build a custom affinity audience?",
        "answer": ["keywords, places, website urls, and app downloads"]
    },
    "120": {
        "question": "which of youtube\u2019s consideration and interest ad formats are skippable ads, bought on a cost-per-view basis?",
        "answer": ["trueview in-stream ads"]
    },
    "121": {
        "question": "in a bumper ad, how much time is usually required to stick the landing?",
        "answer": ["two seconds"]
    },
    "122": {
        "question": "google has created a set of recommendations called abcds you can use to drive performance in your youtube ad campaigns. what does abcd stand for?",
        "answer": ["attract, brand, connect, direct"]
    },
    "123": {
        "question": "what constitutes a video engagement conversion in a trueview for action campaign?",
        "answer": ["user watches 10 seconds of the ad and converts within three days."]
    },
    "124": {
        "question": "which one of google\u2019s data-driven marketing tools helps analyze what people are searching for on youtube?",
        "answer": ["google trends"]
    },
    "125": {
        "question": "zane is managing a youtube campaign for a five-star hotel that competes directly with several other hotels located in the area. the owner would like to use the names of similar hotels as keywords when building the audience for the campaign. what would be the ideal audience solution for zane\u2019s youtube campaign?",
        "answer": ["custom affinity audience"]
    },
    "126": {
        "question": "match the youtube customer with the google audience signal type that helps advertisers connect with that customer.",
        "answer": []
    },
    "127": {
        "question": "what are two events that store visits for trueview for action come from? (choose two.) select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["users who watched 10 seconds of the ad and visited a store location within 30 days.", "users who clicked on an element of the ad and entered a store location within 30days."]
    },
    "128": {
        "question": "how does an advertiser benefit from using think with google?",
        "answer": ["think with google can browse case studies showing how past ad campaigns havesucceeded."]
    },
    "129": {
        "question": "which data can you uncover by running a creative experiment using brand lift?",
        "answer": ["each ad\u2019s impact on brand awareness, consideration, and ad recall"]
    },
    "130": {
        "question": "when it comes to driving action, you should focus on audiences with the strongest level of intent. which of these \u201clowest funnel\u201d audiences is comprised of users who\u2019ve already interacted with your brand, but for some reason didn\u2019t convert?",
        "answer": ["remarketing or customer match"]
    },
    "131": {
        "question": "which trueview ad format is optimized for product awareness?",
        "answer": ["trueview for reach"]
    },
    "132": {
        "question": "what\u2019s one of google and youtube\u2019s awareness products?",
        "answer": ["trueview for reach"]
    },
    "133": {
        "question": "what report should you produce in youtube analytics to see where viewers found your brand\u2019s content?",
        "answer": ["the traffic sources report"]
    },
    "134": {
        "question": "a youtube advertiser is looking to drive direct response objectives. reyna, a youtube googler, explains that youtube for action combines formats powered by smart bidding with intent-rich audiences and measurement capabilities that can help turn engagement on youtube into the actions that matter most. what actions does youtube drive for advertisers?",
        "answer": ["youtube drives actions focused on apps, website activity, lead generation, and offlinestore visits."]
    },
    "135": {
        "question": "how can google\u2019s custom affinity audience signals help an advertiser connect with their target audience?",
        "answer": ["by reaching a one-of-a-kind audience to deliver a niche message at scale."]
    },
    "136": {
        "question": "lou\u2019s client loves the idea of building an audience using search keywords to extend their reach and capture attention when users are making an active purchase decision. which youtube intent audience solution fits this description?",
        "answer": ["custom intent audiences"]
    },
    "137": {
        "question": "which trueview ad format is billed on a cpm basis?",
        "answer": ["trueview for reach"]
    },
    "138": {
        "question": "debra met with a client to discuss adding youtube to their online advertising strategy. she told them how google data and tools can deliver the ideal mix of ad formats, inventory, audience, and measurement solutions to achieve the business outcomes they care about, including awareness and consideration. which other business benefit can youtube help them achieve?",
        "answer": ["action: online conversions, store visits, sales lift"]
    },
    "139": {
        "question": "of the two bidding strategies you can use with your trueview for action campaign, which captures as many valuable actions as possible within a given budget?",
        "answer": ["maximize conversions"]
    },
    "140": {
        "question": "lori manages digital marketing for a travel agency and believes youtube could help the company reach a wider audience. she told her employer that users choose youtube for the rich and diverse content, and because it lets them directly engage the creators they care about. what other reason can lori provide for why users choose youtube?",
        "answer": ["users can connect with a community."]
    },
    "141": {
        "question": "which video format is available on google video partners?",
        "answer": ["trueview in-stream"]
    },
    "142": {
        "question": "as an advertising director for a marketing firm, glenda uses youtube ads to reach her audiences while they\u2019re in their \u201cpersonal primetime.\u201d when is she trying to reach her audience?",
        "answer": ["in highly engaged moments when her audience needs youtube content that\u2019s generaland popular."]
    },
    "143": {
        "question": "the youtube masthead is effective for advertisers with which goal?",
        "answer": ["reach a massive audience around a tentpole event."]
    },
    "144": {
        "question": "you want to use video ad sequencing frameworks. what\u2019s one important data signal to keep in mind when creating your youtube campaign?",
        "answer": ["user intent"]
    },
    "145": {
        "question": "which type of google audience signal analyzes user behavior to identify people who have, for example, recently graduated from college and may need to move?",
        "answer": ["life events"]
    },
    "146": {
        "question": "brandon\u2019s new youtube advertising client has owned the highest-rated theater in town for decades. the theater wants to drive action and take advantage of youtube audience solutions to reach consumers likely to buy a ticket. which youtube audience solution should brandon recommend?",
        "answer": ["customer match audiences"]
    },
    "147": {
        "question": "after a discussion with a google audience specialist, reilly is ready to suggest the use of detailed demographics to her youtube clients. what are two characteristics of detailed demographics? (choose two.) select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["education", "homeownership status"]
    },
    "148": {
        "question": "youtube analytics provides insights from the moment you upload a video. which three basic questions about who\u2019s watching your client\u2019s content will it answer with a single click?",
        "answer": ["age, gender, and geographic location"]
    },
    "149": {
        "question": "ira\u2019s planning a youtube campaign for a new bridal shop looking to attract brides-to-be. he\u2019s sure that intent audience solutions offer the best chance at success. which intent audience solution should he recommend to this particular client?",
        "answer": ["life events"]
    },
    "150": {
        "question": "of the available first-party audience solutions for youtube, which would help you find future customers with audience profiles of 35-54-year-olds, researching motorcycles, likely on an iphone?",
        "answer": ["similar audiences"]
    },
    "151": {
        "question": "yvette\u2019s youtube advertising client owns a boutique offering an exclusive line of designer handbags. she\u2019d like to drive purchases of these handbags using youtube. which youtube format would yvette recommend to her client?",
        "answer": ["trueview for action"]
    },
    "152": {
        "question": "janelle mentions to a new advertiser that innovations in the youtube platform are helping users discover more relevant content. what are two of these innovations? (choose two.) select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["youtube go", "youtube premieres"]
    },
    "153": {
        "question": "which of youtube\u2019s awareness ad formats uses a skippable in-stream format?",
        "answer": ["trueview for reach"]
    },
    "154": {
        "question": "based on google\u2019s analysis of bumper ads, what caused a significant increase in ad recall?",
        "answer": ["when consumers viewed a bumper ad three or more times."]
    },
    "155": {
        "question": "which trueview ad format is optimized for lift in ad recall?",
        "answer": ["trueview in-stream"]
    },
    "156": {
        "question": "miranda, a google video specialist, is recommending youtube to an advertiser who\u2019s looking to drive direct response objectives. with over two billion logged-in monthly users and the highest viewability and audibility on the web at 95%, youtube is a place to drive action. what else makes youtube ideal for driving action?",
        "answer": ["over 40% of global shoppers purchased products they discovered on youtube."]
    },
    "157": {
        "question": "audiences with the strongest level of intent are the most open to being influenced by your message. which audience is made up of people who\u2019ve on google before engaging with your business?",
        "answer": ["custom intent audiences for youtube"]
    },
    "158": {
        "question": "running a creative experiment using brand lift is an excellent way to get the information you need. what\u2019s the first step?",
        "answer": ["draft a hypothesis"]
    },
    "159": {
        "question": "creators choose youtube for the freedom it gives them to use cutting-edge innovations to reach billions of people worldwide and make a living doing what they love. how does youtube help creators earn a living?",
        "answer": ["youtube pays creators to share ads alongside their content."]
    },
    "160": {
        "question": "what\u2019s the best description of affinity audiences on youtube?",
        "answer": ["affinity audiences on youtube reach people based on their lifestyle, interests, andconsumption habits."]
    },
    "161": {
        "question": "what are the four video ad sequencing frameworks advertisers can use to tell great stories on youtube?",
        "answer": ["signals, context, sequence, immersion"]
    },
    "162": {
        "question": "trueview for action ad formats use smart bidding to optimize for specific website actions. to do this, what must be enabled in your google ads account?",
        "answer": ["conversion tracking"]
    },
    "163": {
        "question": "aside from conversion tracking, what\u2019s a requirement for using store visits?",
        "answer": ["the advertiser must have multiple physical locations in eligible countries."]
    },
    "164": {
        "question": "vesta is working on a youtube campaign for a chain of home and garden centers. the owner would like to promote a new line of flowering plants to past customers, using email addresses they provided over the years for marketing purposes. which first-party audience solution would be ideal for vesta\u2019s youtube campaign?",
        "answer": ["customer match audience"]
    },
    "165": {
        "question": "which of youtube\u2019s awareness ad formats is designed to show video ads on websites outside of youtube?",
        "answer": ["outstream video"]
    },
    "166": {
        "question": "match each youtube platform innovation with its description.",
        "answer": []
    },
    "167": {
        "question": "what are two examples of the intent audience solution, life events? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["a home-decor advertiser who wants to reach people who recently bought a home.", "a real-estate advertiser who wants to reach people who recently graduated from medical school."]
    },
    "168": {
        "question": "justine\u2019s client is almost ready to get started with youtube advertising. they\u2019ve asked her to identify the business outcomes youtube can deliver, to ensure they\u2019ll achieve what they\u2019re after with their campaign. which business outcomes can youtube deliver for her client?",
        "answer": ["awareness, consideration, action"]
    },
    "169": {
        "question": "which is a tip google recommends to create an effective bumper ad?",
        "answer": ["focus on a single, simple purpose."]
    },
    "170": {
        "question": "based on the abcds of designing youtube ads, what\u2019s one way to attract viewers?",
        "answer": ["use familiar faces like celebrities, youtube creators, or influencers."]
    },
    "171": {
        "question": "what are two google findings (based on internal research) regarding six-second ads? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["ads that include the product on-screen had higher ad recall.", "six-second ads on youtube drove the same ad recall as 30-second versions on other sites."]
    },
    "172": {
        "question": "as it offers the most attentive audience and proven results, youtube is becoming advertisers\u2019 first choice for building their brands. what\u2019s another reason advertisers choose youtube?",
        "answer": ["youtube is powered by google data and tools."]
    },
    "173": {
        "question": "which bidding strategy works to hit your desired cpa and allows you to achieve more conversions at a stronger roi without manual optimization?",
        "answer": ["target-cost-per-acquisition (tcpa)"]
    },
    "174": {
        "question": "youtube analytics can show you the aggregated totals of the minutes people spent viewing a video over time. which report provides this information?",
        "answer": ["the watch time report"]
    },
    "175": {
        "question": "what can youtube analytics tell you about what people are watching on your client\u2019s channel?",
        "answer": ["real-time views and watch-time"]
    },
    "176": {
        "question": "julian has a client interested in increasing awareness with their youtube campaign. which three youtube audience solutions should he recommend?",
        "answer": ["demographics, affinity, and custom affinity"]
    },
    "177": {
        "question": "dylan\u2019s client produces documentaries. the client wants to understand what makes youtube so appealing to users. dylan explains how youtube lets users engage with the creators they love and become part of an online community of like-minded people. what\u2019s another reason users choose youtube?",
        "answer": ["users choose youtube for rich and diverse content."]
    },
    "178": {
        "question": "for trueview for action, which three events can make up an online conversion?",
        "answer": ["clicks, video engagement, impressions"]
    },
    "179": {
        "question": "youtube can help advertisers achieve three important business outcomes: awareness, consideration, and action. which is a result driven by a youtube advertising campaign to achieve action?",
        "answer": ["online conversions"]
    },
    "180": {
        "question": "which percentage of youtube ads are audible?",
        "answer": ["95%"]
    },
    "181": {
        "question": "annilee has a client who wants to choose youtube audiences that will increase consideration of their products when customers are ready to buy. she knows youtube has two specific audience solutions that can help her accomplish this for the client. what are the two audience solutions? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["life events audiences", "in-market audiences"]
    },
    "182": {
        "question": "aimee\u2019s been researching youtube as a way to promote her content. she was amazed by youtube\u2019s reach and the infrastructure of innovation the platform is committed to building. plus, she loves the freedom creators are given on youtube to express themselves. as a creator, what\u2019s another reason aimee should choose youtube?",
        "answer": ["youtube creators can earn income by sharing ads alongside their content."]
    },
    "183": {
        "question": "your client is interested in testing six-second bumper ads. what are two tips you can share with them about these ads? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["budget time to establish the ad and stick the landing.", "focus on a single, simple purpose."]
    },
    "184": {
        "question": "when measuring offline conversions with trueview for action, a store visit is counted when a user watches 10 seconds of an ad and then visits a store within how many days?",
        "answer": ["30 days"]
    },
    "185": {
        "question": "match the marketing objective with the trueview ad format that\u2019s optimized for that objective.",
        "answer": []
    },
    "186": {
        "question": "which two video formats are available on google video partners? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["bumper ads", "trueview for action"]
    },
    "187": {
        "question": "which type of google audience signal can identify people who are actively researching with the intent to buy?",
        "answer": ["in-market audiences"]
    },
    "188": {
        "question": "how can google\u2019s consumer patterns audience signals help an advertiser connect with their target audience?",
        "answer": ["by reaching people based on where they shop or eat."]
    },
    "189": {
        "question": "what are the tested benefits of bumper ads?",
        "answer": ["bumper ads are effective, efficient, and help businesses reach new people."]
    },
    "190": {
        "question": "how does an advertiser benefit from using google surveys?",
        "answer": ["google surveys can validate the advertiser\u2019s idea through the world\u2019s largest focus group."]
    },
    "191": {
        "question": "which is a key benefit of bumper ads?",
        "answer": ["they deliver comparable brand impact to trueview for advertisers."]
    },
    "192": {
        "question": "leigh\u2019s meeting a makeup distributor ready to launch a new line of mascara. she\u2019s convinced them to use youtube to spread their messaging and believes customer match, which uses customer data provided for marketing purposes, is the right audience solution for their effort. but the client is confused about how the customer match process works. leigh breaks it down into a three-step process to make it easier to understand. what\u2019s the three-step customer match process?",
        "answer": ["upload data, match the data, and create audience lists"]
    },
    "193": {
        "question": "match the trueview ad format with its corresponding bidding type. (not all options are used.)",
        "answer": []
    },
    "194": {
        "question": "based on the abcds of designing youtube ads, how does google recommend that you open with impact?",
        "answer": ["front-load the story arc, focus on framing, and use familiar faces."]
    },
    "195": {
        "question": "what is one reason an advertiser would choose youtube for action?",
        "answer": ["over 55% of people search for a product on google, then use youtube to learn more about itbefore they purchase."]
    },
    "196": {
        "question": "what are the two types of bidding available for trueview for action to help drive conversions? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["maximize conversions", "target cost-per-acquisition"]
    },
    "197": {
        "question": "in the abcd recommendations google created for youtube advertising, the a stands for attract and the b for brand. what do the c and d stand for?",
        "answer": ["connect and direct"]
    },
    "198": {
        "question": "nadia\u2019s client is concerned about losing their presence in customer living rooms. nadia knows youtube would be an excellent solution for the client\u2019s problem. what\u2019s a compelling reason youtube would be a good solution for her client to consider?",
        "answer": ["the living room, once ruled by broadcast tv and physical media, is youtube\u2019s fastest-growingplatform."]
    },
    "199": {
        "question": "which youtube analytics report can give you the average view duration for all of the videos on your brand\u2019s channel?",
        "answer": ["the audience retention report"]
    },
    "200": {
        "question": "what\u2019s a key benefit of trueview for reach?",
        "answer": ["it optimizes for impressions instead of views."]
    },
    "201": {
        "question": "ajay\u2019s meeting with a client who\u2019s considering youtube advertising. the client wants to better understand why users choose youtube. ajay shares information on youtube\u2019s extensive reach and the opportunity it provides for users to connect with a community. what are two other reasons users choose youtube? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["users can connect with creators directly.", "it showcases rich and diverse content."]
    },
    "202": {
        "question": "how can google\u2019s in-market audience signals help an advertiser connect with their target audience?",
        "answer": ["by reaching people performing searches with the intent to buy or searching for competitiveproducts."]
    },
    "203": {
        "question": "leigh\u2019s client, a car dealership, asks her to reach highly qualified consumers ready to make a purchase. which intent audience on youtube should leigh use?",
        "answer": ["in-market audiences"]
    },
    "204": {
        "question": "which of youtube\u2019s awareness ad formats can use the cpd bidding approach?",
        "answer": ["masthead"]
    },
    "205": {
        "question": "in google\u2019s abcds, what are two recommendations for connecting with viewers? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["leverage the power of audio in your ads to lift brand awareness.", "increase your ad\u2019s pacing to capture attention and keep it longer."]
    },
    "206": {
        "question": "what information can youtube analytics provide about where people are watching your videos?",
        "answer": ["traffic source and device"]
    },
    "207": {
        "question": "which storytelling method entices users with short ads, reinforces their interest with longer ads, and then repeats the messaging to prompt action?",
        "answer": ["tease, amplify, echo"]
    },
    "208": {
        "question": "audra handles youtube strategy for a popular concert venue that would like to run youtube campaigns aimed at fans of the musicians they\u2019ve booked this summer. which type of audience solution should audra recommend for this client?",
        "answer": ["custom affinity"]
    },
    "209": {
        "question": "which one of google\u2019s data-driven tools is part of google analytics solutions?",
        "answer": ["google surveys"]
    },
    "210": {
        "question": "which type of google audience signal reaches consumers on youtube based on their consumption habits?",
        "answer": ["consumer patterns"]
    },
    "211": {
        "question": "of the storytelling methods recommended for youtube campaigns, which one uses a long-piece format creative ad to deliver a brand\u2019s messaging and shorter ads to reinforce it?",
        "answer": ["the follow-up storytelling method"]
    },
    "212": {
        "question": "myra wants to reach consumers her company already has in their crm. which intent audience solutions on youtube should myra select when building her campaign?",
        "answer": ["customer match and similar audiences"]
    },
    "213": {
        "question": "which video ad sequencing framework is focused on where a viewer is and what they\u2019re doing when they interact with a youtube ad?",
        "answer": ["context"]
    },
    "214": {
        "question": "landon works for an online marketing firm and believes that youtube will be an effective addition to his client\u2019s advertising strategy given its extensive reach of over two billion monthly active users and recent innovations that increase usership. which two next generation innovations can landon share with his client? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["youtube on tv screens", "mobile live streaming"]
    },
    "215": {
        "question": "mira explained to a new client how youtube can help brands reach the most attractive customers and prospects by helping them tap into real-time data and powerful signals to be more effective storytellers. which other benefit of youtube audience solutions should she mention?",
        "answer": ["cross-device reach"]
    },
    "216": {
        "question": "when your goal is driving action, you focus on audiences with the strongest level of intent. match each \u201clowest funnel\u201d audience type with its description.",
        "answer": []
    },
    "217": {
        "question": "which trueview ad format is billed by cpa?",
        "answer": ["trueview for action"]
    },
    "218": {
        "question": "ramone\u2019s client is allocating some of her advertising budget to youtube to take advantage of affinity audiences. she wants to know more about affinity audiences before committing any resources. which of the following isn\u2019t a step google uses to build an affinity audience for youtube?",
        "answer": ["emails to sign users up"]
    },
    "219": {
        "question": "what are the three key reasons advertisers choose youtube to help build their brands?",
        "answer": ["youtube has the most engaged audience, is powered by google data and tools, and delivers proven results."]
    },
    "220": {
        "question": "which marketer would be an ideal client for trueview for action?",
        "answer": ["a marketer who wants to use custom intent audiences to deliver a customizable and consistent call-to-action, driving clicks and website actions."]
    },
    "221": {
        "question": "which of youtube\u2019s ad formats target high-intent audiences at key moments of making a buying decision, and help them make the purchase?",
        "answer": ["trueview for action ads"]
    },
    "222": {
        "question": "aaron\u2019s client is an architect who\u2019d like to use youtube to reach more potential customers. the client believes one generic ad should be enough to do the job, but aaron knows that\u2019s a questionable approach. what can aaron tell the client about ad relevance on youtube to change his mind?",
        "answer": ["viewers pay three times more attention to relevant ads than those aimed at generic audiences."]
    },
    "223": {
        "question": "hiro\u2019s construction client wants to reach people who\u2019ve shown an interest in purchasing a home. which intent audience solution should hiro recommend?",
        "answer": ["life events audience"]
    },
    "224": {
        "question": "to assist advertisers using youtube, google created a set of recommendations based on successful campaigns, known as the abcds. match each recommendation with its meaning.",
        "answer": []
    },
    "225": {
        "question": "which two are ideal advertisers for custom intent audiences? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["advertisers looking to expand their non-brand search campaigns.", "advertisers using conversion tracking in their video campaigns."]
    },
    "226": {
        "question": "which two google audience solutions use first-party data? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["remarketing", "custom affinity"]
    },
    "227": {
        "question": "which is a key benefit of trueview discovery?",
        "answer": ["it reaches users scrolling down the youtube home page."]
    },
    "228": {
        "question": "how does an advertiser benefit from using google trends?",
        "answer": ["google trends can discover the top questions their target audience is asking."]
    },
    "229": {
        "question": "what counts as a view-through conversion in a trueview for action campaign?",
        "answer": ["user sees just an impression of the ad and converts within 24 hours."]
    },
    "230": {
        "question": "janine recommends using a customer match audience on youtube so a client can reach existing customers. where does janine upload customer information, such as e-mail addresses, to start the customer match process?",
        "answer": ["google ads and display &amp; video 360"]
    },
    "231": {
        "question": "local inventory ads are ideal for which business?",
        "answer": ["flowers by beth, an online floral shop that just opened a brick-and-mortar location."]
    },
    "232": {
        "question": "dante is the owner of homethings, a shop that sells home goods. he just launched a local catalog ad campaign. where are two places a consumer might encounter dante\u2019s local catalog ad? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["in any of three-million sites and apps.", "on a website during mobile browsing."]
    },
    "233": {
        "question": "what\u2019s one way to increase your business profitability?",
        "answer": ["make use of data to improve your predictive decision-making."]
    },
    "234": {
        "question": "today\u2019s consumers are more demanding and less patient than before. what\u2019s one way to grow your business by delivering the type of service they expect?",
        "answer": ["provide a seamless experience, using data to connect and personalize content."]
    },
    "235": {
        "question": "a single branch of simpson shoes has been operating since 1917. they recently ran their first online ad and after its launch the owner wanted to see the ad online. where should the owner search to find his local inventory ad?",
        "answer": ["when he is nearby simpson shoes searching online for an in-stock style."]
    },
    "236": {
        "question": "what\u2019s one unique feature of local catalog ads?",
        "answer": ["they use data from local inventory ads."]
    },
    "237": {
        "question": "what are two ways google ads reporting for shopping campaigns help monitor how your products are performing at many levels of granularity? (choose two.)",
        "answer": []
    },
    "238": {
        "question": "how can advertisers use shopping campaign ads in order to drive sales?",
        "answer": ["by taking advantage of google customer reviews, merchant promotions, and product ratings."]
    },
    "239": {
        "question": "susan is the marketing director for a chain of bakeries that make artisan bread. she\u2019s looking for an online advertising strategy to raise the bakery chain\u2019s presence in their market. how can a showcase shopping ad help susan promote her brand?",
        "answer": ["by presenting a selection of their artisan breads to potential customers."]
    },
    "240": {
        "question": "which statement is true about shopping ads?",
        "answer": ["they use an easy-to-understand format to give shoppers all the information they need at a glance."]
    },
    "241": {
        "question": "how do google shopping ads drive engagement with potential customers to make their shopping experiences as seamless as possible?",
        "answer": ["customers can view and interact with attractive and engaging ads that give them a better sense of the product before they open the ad."]
    },
    "242": {
        "question": "anne sells homemade artisan soaps. she just brought her brick-and-mortar store online, and she\u2019s considering running a local inventory ad with google. how could a local inventory ad help anne expand her business?",
        "answer": ["by attracting potential customers who usually search for artisan soaps."]
    },
    "243": {
        "question": "what\u2019s one way the increase in mobile apps, screens, and other surfaces has changed how consumers shop?",
        "answer": ["consumers are buying from whichever platform or brand gives the best experience."]
    },
    "244": {
        "question": "tom wants a way to automatically create ads and simplify campaign management, using his resources and google\u2019s machine learning to create a variety of ads that will be displayed across networks. which of tom\u2019s resources are needed to accomplish his aims as part of his smart shopping campaign?",
        "answer": ["account product feed and uploaded assets"]
    },
    "245": {
        "question": "joan sells fashion watches online, and she\u2019s had great success with google shopping campaigns. now, she\u2019d like her business to do even better! how can shopping ads make joan\u2019s shopping ads even more profitable?",
        "answer": ["with shopping ads, she can use merchant promotions to encourage shoppers to buy."]
    },
    "246": {
        "question": "gina owns a woodworking shop that makes custom cabinets. she uploads data to her google merchant center to help create ads from her inventory. what data does a shopping campaign use from her merchant center feed to place gina\u2019s ads?",
        "answer": ["her cabinet\u2019s attributes, such as price"]
    },
    "247": {
        "question": "boards by ben is a surf shop that\u2019s always used a google-hosted storefront. they\u2019re looking at ways to bring shoppers into their store with local inventory ads. what\u2019s one benefit boards by ben can access by using a local inventory ad?",
        "answer": ["the ability to show his products and store information to shoppers who are within 30 miles (48 km) of their store and searching on google."]
    },
    "248": {
        "question": "kathi, the owner of klothes for kats, is excited about the launch of her first local catalog ad. she remembers there are a few different views within the ad type. which view will kathi\u2019s potential customers be able to browse on her new local catalog ad?",
        "answer": ["map view, where potential customers can see the klothes for kats logo, store information, and in-stock products."]
    },
    "249": {
        "question": "office king is a well-established business that\u2019s been using print ads for their office-supply store for years. how can local catalog ads help office king?",
        "answer": ["local catalog ads can extend officeking\u2019s ad reach outside the mailbox."]
    },
    "250": {
        "question": "carrie owns a boutique shop that sells decorative, handmade pottery. she\u2019s choosing an online ad campaign to allow a seamless shopping experience for her potential customers. what\u2019s one benefit that shopping campaign ads offer carrie?",
        "answer": ["they\u2019re visual, and provide detailed information about what she\u2019s selling before someone even opens her ads."]
    },
    "251": {
        "question": "the website for your retail business is receiving a lot of visitors, but few of them are looking at more than one page. what\u2019s most likely to be the problem?",
        "answer": ["your website is too slow to load quickly on mobile devices."]
    },
    "252": {
        "question": "mary owns an automotive parts store, and wants to differentiate her brand. she\u2019s considering launching new ads with google to influence automotive shoppers at the start of their purchasing journey. if mary went with showcase shopping ads, where would her customers see the ads? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["at the top of google searches on desktop computers.", "at the top of google searches on mobile browsers."]
    },
    "253": {
        "question": "glenn\u2019s new business is growing slowly, but he\u2019s worried about cash flow. how can smart shopping campaigns help glenn\u2019s business?",
        "answer": ["by automatically attempting to maximize conversion value."]
    },
    "254": {
        "question": "chris is the marketing director for keys & strings, a company that makes custom pianos. keys & strings sells pianos through their website. chris decides to use a showcase shopping ad to advertise his brand of pianos. who\u2019s chris trying to reach with his showcase shopping ad?",
        "answer": ["potential customers who are early in their online search."]
    },
    "255": {
        "question": "sherman wants to be sure potential customers on mobile devices will see his shopping ads, especially if their screens are small. in which position(s) on a search results page will sherman\u2019s shopping campaign ads appear on mobile devices?",
        "answer": ["only at the top of the search results."]
    },
    "256": {
        "question": "carey\u2019s used google ads for some time, but he recently found he doesn\u2019t have time to manage multiple campaigns effectively. how can smart shopping campaigns reduce carey\u2019s ads management workload?",
        "answer": ["smart shopping campaigns automate ad placement and bidding."]
    },
    "257": {
        "question": "how do smart shopping campaigns use automated bidding and placements, and machine learning to show a variety of the most relevant ads across google networks to potential customers?",
        "answer": []
    },
    "258": {
        "question": "books by brock is a used bookstore that\u2019s always used text ads. they\u2019re looking at ways to optimize their experience with google ads, and considering local inventory ads. what\u2019s a unique feature of local inventory ads that can benefit books by brock?",
        "answer": ["they can be used with merchant or google-hosted storefronts."]
    },
    "259": {
        "question": "officeplus is a well-established business that\u2019s been running print ads for their office-supply store for years. you\u2019ve been asked to present local catalog ads as a potential solution for their consideration. what\u2019s one way local catalog ads would benefit officeplus?",
        "answer": ["by extending their reach beyond print."]
    },
    "260": {
        "question": "what\u2019s one way to create a seamless experience for your retail customers?",
        "answer": ["make sure that items added to a cart are saved for later visits."]
    },
    "261": {
        "question": "shopping ads help online businesses drive sales even before potential customers open ads for their products. that\u2019s because shoppers are more likely to complete a purchase under what conditions?",
        "answer": ["when they\u2019re better informed prior to opening the ad."]
    },
    "262": {
        "question": "maureen\u2019s company sells first-aid kits for use in everyday situations. because kits come in many sizes, with many features, and at many price points, maureen finds it difficult to differentiate her company\u2019s offerings from those of other vendors. worse, potential customers may find it hard to compare search results for her products and prices with those of other vendors. how can shopping ads address these concerns?",
        "answer": ["her shopping ads will only show a photo, price, title, store name, and product details. customers can know at a glance if her kits fit their needs and budget."]
    },
    "263": {
        "question": "how can smart shopping campaigns help businesses easily promote their products without making large demands on their time?",
        "answer": ["smart shopping campaigns automate key features of ad creation and placement."]
    },
    "264": {
        "question": "jonah\u2019s surf shop has been running google ads for years, and now they\u2019re interested in introducing a new type of online ad. which potential customer could jonah reach by running local inventory ads?",
        "answer": ["rob, who wants to see a specific board in-store before he\u2019ll purchase it."]
    },
    "265": {
        "question": "alice owns a business selling a range of backpacks for business users and worldwide travelers. she spends most of her time managing stock levels, staff, and her company\u2019s finances, so she\u2019s worried that running google ads might be too time-consuming. how do smart shopping campaigns simplify campaign management?",
        "answer": ["smart shopping campaigns automate budget allocation, targeting, ad creation, and bidding."]
    },
    "266": {
        "question": "what are two features that can appear on shopping campaign ads in order to drive online sales? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["product ratings", "free shipping"]
    },
    "267": {
        "question": "which type of automated bidding strategy is target cost-per-acquisition (cpa)?",
        "answer": ["conversion-focused bidding"]
    },
    "268": {
        "question": "which statement is true about local catalog ads?",
        "answer": ["local catalog ads are easy-to-browse display ads that showcase multiple products."]
    },
    "269": {
        "question": "how do shopping ads help improve qualified leads over standard text ads as part of a seamless retail experience?",
        "answer": ["shopping ads are visually enticing and display detailed product information before the ad is clicked."]
    },
    "270": {
        "question": "lance, the owner of a long-standing antique toy shop, hears the youngsters in his shop talk about how effective the display ad from toys by tammy was. he becomes interested in accessing the google display network (gdn). what\u2019s one way lance could use the gdn?",
        "answer": ["by running a campaign of local catalog ads."]
    },
    "271": {
        "question": "alex has only a limited budget, and he needs to use it effectively. how do smart shopping campaigns simplify the process of advertising with a limited budget?",
        "answer": ["by automating bidding to maximize conversion value."]
    },
    "272": {
        "question": "aaron\u2019s been running shopping ads for some time, and he\u2019s interested in experimenting with ways to improve sales performance by using additional features. which benefit might he obtain by using merchant promotions?",
        "answer": ["when he adds promotions to products he sells on google, shoppers will see a \u201cspecial offer\u201d link."]
    },
    "273": {
        "question": "which type of automated bidding strategy is enhanced cost-per-click (ecpc)?",
        "answer": ["conversion-focused bidding"]
    },
    "274": {
        "question": "which statement describes modern shopping behavior?",
        "answer": ["people are buying more often, but fewer items each time."]
    },
    "275": {
        "question": "courtney\u2019s online campaigns have produced plenty of clicks, but not as many sales as she expected. how can shopping ads help make sure the clicks the ads receive come from customers more interested in her products?",
        "answer": ["by providing product data and details before the ad is opened."]
    },
    "276": {
        "question": "how do product images and prices contribute to a seamless shopping experience in shopping ads?",
        "answer": ["potential customers can quickly see whether the product fits their expectations."]
    },
    "277": {
        "question": "office king is a well-established business that\u2019s been running print ads for their office-supply store for years. their ceo, xin, is exploring the possibility of expanding into online advertising. he asks you to provide a comparison of traditional print ads and local catalog ads. what\u2019s one distinguishing feature of local catalog ads?",
        "answer": ["they enable officeking to measure store visits."]
    },
    "278": {
        "question": "susan is the marketing director for a chain of bakeries that make artisan bread. she chose a showcase shopping ad to promote her company\u2019s brand. what will susan need to create a successful showcase shopping ad?",
        "answer": ["curated lifestyle images and creative copy to set her products apart from the competition."]
    },
    "279": {
        "question": "how can a shopping ad help retail businesses create ads that encourage your potential customers to visit your brick-and-mortar stores?",
        "answer": ["shopping ads let you surface your local inventory, and share store details for users searching near a store."]
    },
    "280": {
        "question": "ben sells homemade artisan soaps at a mall kiosk called fresh soaps. he\u2019s considering running a local inventory ad with google. what unique type of information would ben\u2019s local inventory ad show?",
        "answer": ["brick-and-mortar location"]
    },
    "281": {
        "question": "how can smart shopping campaigns make promoting your business less time-consuming and easier to manage?",
        "answer": ["by automatically uploading product details from manufacturers\u2019 websites."]
    },
    "282": {
        "question": "jodi creates custom hair pieces. she just launched her first online advertising campaign, and it included a showcase shopping ad. where will jodi\u2019s showcase shopping ad be featured?",
        "answer": ["at the top of a google search for \u201ccute hair accessories.\u201d"]
    },
    "283": {
        "question": "gemma wants to promote her online handbag business to a wide audience but she\u2019s busy creating handbags for her clients, and has little time to manage the specifics of an advertising campaign. how can smart shopping campaigns help her achieve this?",
        "answer": ["by showing her ads across multiple audiences and networks."]
    },
    "284": {
        "question": "george wants to advertise online, but his profit margins are tight. he\u2019s worried the spend won\u2019t provide the income he needs. how can smart shopping campaigns help george get the results he needs?",
        "answer": ["smart shopping campaigns can be set with a target return on ad spend."]
    },
    "285": {
        "question": "peter has a new online store selling electric bikes and spares. he wants to promote his business, but with a simple solution that provides a wide reach for his products. how can smart shopping campaigns help peter with his sales?",
        "answer": ["by automating bidding and ad placement across networks."]
    },
    "286": {
        "question": "chris is the marketing director for keys & strings, a company that makes custom pianos. keys & strings sells their pianos through their website, and has a small but loyal customer base. chris is tasked with increasing the size of keys & strings\u2019 customer base. why is a showcase shopping ad the right choice for chris?",
        "answer": ["it shows products early in the search process, to help customers discover your brand while customers are looking for what to buy."]
    },
    "287": {
        "question": "which two product attributes are shown in google shopping campaign ads to help engage potential customers with relevant information? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["image", "price"]
    },
    "288": {
        "question": "a single branch of simpson shoes has been operating since 1917. as they consider moving into online marketing, the owner, bert simpson, wants to focus on a specific, potential customer type. which potential customer would benefit from simpson shoes running a local inventory ad?",
        "answer": ["brandon, who does an online search for men\u2019s shoes near the simpson shoes store because he needs a pair of dress shoes for an event this evening. "]
    },
    "289": {
        "question": "rhonda sells homemade artisan soaps. she just opened her first brick-and-mortar shop, soaps by rhonda, and she\u2019s considering running a local inventory ad with google. what does rhonda need to run a successful local inventory ad?",
        "answer": []
    },
    "290": {
        "question": "where can shopping campaign ads appear on desktop search results pages?",
        "answer": ["only at the top or to the right of search results."]
    },
    "291": {
        "question": "you use google shopping ads to promote customer engagement with your products. how can this increase your business\u2019s presence in searches?",
        "answer": ["shopping ads let more than one of your products be shown for a given search, and a text ad for your products could appear at the same time."]
    },
    "292": {
        "question": "susan is the marketing director for a chain of bakeries that make artisan bread. she recently did a photoshoot of the company\u2019s line of breads, and is looking for an online advertising solution to promote their brand. why are showcase shopping ads the right choice for susan?",
        "answer": ["they give susan the opportunity to inspire customers through beautiful lifestyle images and custom copy."]
    },
    "293": {
        "question": "which two brand qualities are today\u2019s consumers most likely to find helpful? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["providing a seamless experience.", "making it easy to discover new things."]
    },
    "294": {
        "question": "cheryl is the owner of homethings, a shop that sells home goods. you, as her marketing intern, are describing the various google ad offerings. what\u2019s an accurate description of local catalog ads you could give cheryl?",
        "answer": ["they\u2019re mobile-based ads that showcase multiple products."]
    },
    "295": {
        "question": "betsysbookbar is a book store and cafe that\u2019s had a brick-and-mortar location for years. they\u2019re looking at ways to move into online marketing, and want to optimize their experience with google ads. what are two options for using local inventory ads that are available to betsysbookbar? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["use a google-hosted local storefront.", "create a customized merchant-hosted local storefront."]
    },
    "296": {
        "question": "which product attributes in shopping campaign ads are important for giving shoppers the most meaningful information needed, all at a single glance?",
        "answer": ["product image, price, and store name"]
    },
    "297": {
        "question": "which two features, available as additions to shopping campaign ads, can benefit marketers and drive sales? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["google customer reviews", "merchant promotions"]
    },
    "298": {
        "question": "what\u2019s one way to use google\u2019s data across all platforms, to increase your retail company\u2019s performance and profitability?",
        "answer": ["personalize the customer experience wherever they may be searching."]
    },
    "299": {
        "question": "isabella owns a bookstore and has been running a google shopping campaign for several months. she\u2019d like to identify growth opportunities in her business. how can the reporting feature in google shopping ads help isabella get the information she needs?",
        "answer": ["she can use impression-share data and the bid simulator tool."]
    },
    "300": {
        "question": "wade\u2019s the owner of homethings, a shop that sells home cash-and-carry goods. he says he\u2019s interested in expanding his marketing reach. you suggest running a local catalog ad. what\u2019s an accurate description of local catalog ads you could give wade?",
        "answer": ["they\u2019re visual, easy-to-browse display ads."]
    },
    "301": {
        "question": "a single branch of simpson shoes has been operating since 1917. a new marketing team member suggested they look into local inventory ads. the owner, bert simpson, is concerned about where potential customers might see the ad. where would the simpson shoes local inventory ad appear?",
        "answer": ["in google search from a device within 30 miles (48 km) of the simpson shoes location."]
    },
    "302": {
        "question": "brenda designs bespoke furniture, and just finalized her first showcase shopping ad. she wants to show the ad to her family. how can brenda find her showcase shopping ad?",
        "answer": ["it promotes brand awareness, so it will appear at the top of search results after a google search for \u201ccustom ottoman.\u201d"]
    },
    "303": {
        "question": "how has consumer shopping behavior changed in recent years?",
        "answer": ["people are buying fewer items more frequently."]
    },
    "304": {
        "question": "how can running a local inventory ad increase your return on investment (roi)?",
        "answer": ["by bringing online shoppers into your brick-and-mortar store."]
    },
    "305": {
        "question": "your website data shows that many visitors place items in their shopping carts, but fail to complete the purchase. you want to grow your business by increasing sales. what should you do first?",
        "answer": ["remove friction: make sure the checkout process is working and easy to use."]
    },
    "306": {
        "question": "how does google ads help a business organize inventory, letting the business match its advertising goals?",
        "answer": ["the business can browse their product inventory directly in google ads and create product groups for the items they want to bid on."]
    },
    "307": {
        "question": "lance has been running local inventory ads to promote his antique toy shop. he\u2019s considering running additional ad campaigns with google. what\u2019s an easy next step lance can take to expand his brand\u2019s reach?",
        "answer": ["use local inventory feed data to reach viewers with local catalog ads."]
    },
    "308": {
        "question": "greg owns a company, keys & strings, that makes custom pianos. keys & strings sells their pianos through their website. greg would like to increase sales of his brand of pianos. why would greg use a showcase shopping ad?",
        "answer": ["to engage customers at the point in their purchase journey where they\u2019re discovering what to buy and where to buy it."]
    },
    "309": {
        "question": "what\u2019s one way to make good use of data to accelerate your business and improve profitability?",
        "answer": ["create personalized product recommendations."]
    },
    "310": {
        "question": "if klothes for kats uses local catalog ads, their ads can be shown in different views. which two statements are true about views that are available in local catalog ads? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["map view, where potential customers can find klothes for kats\u2019 brick-and-mortar location.", "main view, where consumers can quickly see key information about klothes for kats."]
    },
    "311": {
        "question": "what can automated bidding help an advertiser improve?",
        "answer": ["performance"]
    },
    "312": {
        "question": "how do smart shopping campaigns work to maximize conversion value while simplifying campaign management across networks, leveraging machine learning?",
        "answer": ["by automatically optimizing bids, audiences, and products displayed."]
    },
    "313": {
        "question": "angelo owns a bookstore and has been running a google shopping campaign for several months. he needs to monitor how different books are performing. how can angelo get the information he needs?",
        "answer": ["angelo can see how many clicks a specific book received by filtering his products view."]
    },
    "314": {
        "question": "google ads shopping certification \u2013 list of latest and updated questions",
        "answer": ["shopping campaigns, which promote her products by giving consumers detailed informationabout what she is selling before they click her ad."]
    },
    "315": {
        "question": "what are two ways to grow your business by helping consumers who want to buy at a local, physical store? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["allow shoppers to buy online and pick up at the store.", "provide opening hours, locations, and stock levels."]
    },
    "316": {
        "question": "you operate an online retail website and have google tag manager set up to manage your tags on your site. you now want to set up sitewide conversion tracking tags in order to evaluate the effectiveness of your next google ad campaign. which step is required in order to do this setup?",
        "answer": ["add the conversion linker tag to your landing page urls."]
    },
    "317": {
        "question": "which is an example of a purchase metric that can be tracked?",
        "answer": ["return on ad spend"]
    },
    "318": {
        "question": "brenda\u2019s meeting with the web developer of her retail website concerning the integration of conversion tracking using google ads. the web developer needs to set up conversion tracking tags. what\u2019s required to accomplish this?",
        "answer": ["auto-tagging must be turned on in all of her google ads."]
    },
    "319": {
        "question": "tom is an advertising executive at a car company. before beginning work on a video advertising campaign for a new economy car, he creates key performance indicators for the campaign. what\u2019s tom defining?",
        "answer": ["media objectives"]
    },
    "320": {
        "question": "sometimes it is not possible to measure the success of a google ads campaign that is aggregated across multiple channels, as is the case with measuring brand awareness and brand favorability. why is it difficult to determine performance across multiple channels?",
        "answer": ["multiple channels may use different tools to measure brand lift."]
    },
    "321": {
        "question": "well-managed, verified google my business listings get five times more views than those that are unclaimed. how can you verify a location in google my business?",
        "answer": ["you can verify <a>with a phone call, an e-mail, or a postcard through the mail</a>."]
    },
    "322": {
        "question": "an event tag is a code snippet that works directly with a global site tag to track customer actions specified by an advertiser as conversions. which types of event tags can be created?",
        "answer": ["page load and click"]
    },
    "323": {
        "question": "which google offering could you use to measure the number of people who click or view your ads and later visit your business location?",
        "answer": ["store visits"]
    },
    "324": {
        "question": "you recently released a mobile app for your online retail store. you\u2019re reviewing the totals across all conversions in your google ads account using the campaign report in google ads. you want to see how effectively your new app is producing conversions for app installs and first opens. which action will accomplish this?",
        "answer": ["segment the data by conversion action."]
    },
    "325": {
        "question": "allen is a marketing manager who received a series of ads from his creative team. he wants to use a/b testing to find the ads in the series that yield the best results. which type of ads will allen compare?",
        "answer": ["ads used in identical ways, on the same channels, and directed at the same audience."]
    },
    "326": {
        "question": "mary is a marketing manager for a nationwide vegan restaurant chain. she wants to reach potential customers across two media channels focusing on specific audience behaviors. which two channels could she choose to reach her desired objective? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["video", "display"]
    },
    "327": {
        "question": "google marketing platform is as effective for small businesses as it is for enterprises. in fact, only two products aren\u2019t available in the small business version of google marketing platform. what are these two products? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["search ads 360", "display &amp; video 360"]
    },
    "328": {
        "question": "levi is an experienced marketing strategist for a software company that sells a learning platform to public schools. he has developed healthy individual measurement habits that drive his success in constantly evolving his company\u2019s marketing strategies to the changing needs of the schools. which two habits has levi developed to help him evaluate and adapt his marketing strategies? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["he segments data using his company\u2019s crm dashboards, giving his organization access to data that powers their decision-making.", "he encourages learning from failure, which is necessary for testing the possibilities and for learning what does not work."]
    },
    "329": {
        "question": "sarah\u2019s a digital marketing consultant. with 90% of sales still taking place in a physical location, she knows her clients need to reach customers throughout their journey to ensure the best chance at a sale. those customers need to find her client\u2019s products across multiple channels. which type of marketing strategy can sarah use to drive sales to her client\u2019s physical locations?",
        "answer": ["an online-to-offline strategy to drive offline sales with online ads."]
    },
    "330": {
        "question": "cory owns a custom purse-design business. he launched an advertising campaign featuring purses made of environmentally friendly materials. he\u2019s followed his customers through their entire journeys. what should cory do to move his customer journey forward when a potential customer shows a strong interest in a product?",
        "answer": ["offer them a specific call to action"]
    },
    "331": {
        "question": "kevin created an app with firebase that links the inventory of his business to his online store, which he\u2019s promoting on google ads. he wants to track sales from the app and needs to link his firebase and google ads accounts. which permissions will kevin\u2019s google account need to link firebase to google ads?",
        "answer": ["owner on the project permissions in firebase"]
    },
    "332": {
        "question": "you want to track first opens for your mobile app. your app uses the firebase sdk. place the steps in the correct order to accomplish this within google ads. (the first step should be on top.)",
        "answer": []
    },
    "333": {
        "question": "google my business provides businesses with opportunities for connecting with their customers online. what are two ways google my business would help engage your customers? (choose two.)",
        "answer": []
    },
    "334": {
        "question": "richard\u2019s a marketing executive for an online leather-goods retailer. he\u2019s focused on data measurement to drive sales of his company\u2019s belt lines. he turned to google\u2019s automated machine learning to help his company gain a competitive advantage in the marketplace. what\u2019s an important first step that richard must take to succeed at automation?",
        "answer": ["he first breaks down his organization\u2019s data silos to ensure data quality. that lets the correct data get recorded by google\u2019s machine-learning algorithm."]
    },
    "335": {
        "question": "sidney\u2019s in his google ads account and wants to analyze how effectively his video ads drive conversions on his website. he\u2019s currently reviewing the attribution report. what information will this report provide him?",
        "answer": ["data about the customer paths that lead to conversions for his online business."]
    },
    "336": {
        "question": "how does google my business help businesses reach more customers when it matters most? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["by providing insights on customer behavior.", "by engaging their customers online."]
    },
    "337": {
        "question": "you\u2019re setting up offline conversion tracking. you need to to upload offline data into your google ads account. which two formats are supported? (choose two.)",
        "answer": []
    },
    "338": {
        "question": "by linking a google my business account with a google ads account, you\u2019re able to create location extensions. which information can location extensions display?",
        "answer": ["your address, a link to your location on google maps, or the distance to your business"]
    },
    "339": {
        "question": "a flower delivery business wants to raise their overall sales volume to increase profit. after analyzing their costs, they choose their most popular line of flower arrangements and run a promotion on those arrangements. how would this promotion lead to higher profits?",
        "answer": ["by lowering the price of the flower arrangements to increase demand."]
    },
    "340": {
        "question": "which statement describes linear attribution?",
        "answer": ["it distributes credit evenly to every single touch-point in a buyer\u2019s journey."]
    },
    "341": {
        "question": "your company\u2019s created a collection of two-to-three years\u2019 worth of weekly data for every driver of sales, including all marketing channels, but also across areas like price promotions, distribution, and product changes. you can now analyze roi (return on investment) for each media channel to determine the ones you should continue to invest in. which analysis technique have you used?",
        "answer": ["media mix model"]
    },
    "342": {
        "question": "after you\u2019ve successfully installed a conversion tag on your website or app and a conversion action has taken place, where\u2019s conversion data viewed within google ads?",
        "answer": ["in the campaigns tab, under the conversions column"]
    },
    "343": {
        "question": "mary\u2019s a marketing manager for a nationwide restaurant chain. she\u2019s considering which channel she should use to advertise her restaurant\u2019s new menu upgrades. she decides to use traditional channels. which traditional channel should may use to reach a broad audience?",
        "answer": ["television"]
    },
    "344": {
        "question": "jerran is a marketing manager at an advertising agency. his client would like to track contact form submissions originating from their google ads account. the client has a global site tag successfully installed, so jerran can use an event tag to track this conversion action. which type of event tag should jerran use?",
        "answer": ["a page load event tag"]
    },
    "345": {
        "question": "sara is analyzing the conversion data of her video ad campaign in google ads. she wants to see a summary of, on average, how many days, ad clicks, and ad impressions it took users to convert a customer. which report will provide her with this information?",
        "answer": ["the attribution overview report"]
    },
    "346": {
        "question": "levi is an experienced marketing strategist for a software company that sells a learning platform to public schools. he has developed healthy individual measurement habits that drive his success in constantly evolving his company\u2019s marketing strategies to the changing needs of the schools. what are two habits levi has developed to help him evaluate and adapt his marketing strategies? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["he runs tests continuously, increasing data points that help inform important strategic decisions.", "he starts his day by looking at how well he is doing on his company\u2019s key performance indicators."]
    },
    "347": {
        "question": "deshawn uses google ads. he wants to enable website call conversion tracking so he can see how his current ad campaign is driving users to call the number on his business website. how are the calls tracked to deshawn\u2019s account?",
        "answer": ["a dynamically created google forwarding number"]
    },
    "348": {
        "question": "measuring conversion actions can help you better understand how users connect with your brand. which are conversion actions you can measure?",
        "answer": ["purchase, lead, page view, and sign-up"]
    },
    "349": {
        "question": "an executive at a clothing company is looking to define overarching goals for his company. what\u2019s the executive defining?",
        "answer": ["business objectives"]
    },
    "350": {
        "question": "darian has a gourmet cupcake business and needs a website to compete with the other bakeries in his area. he has a google my business listing and wants to use the website builder to create a personalized design for his business. what are the steps, in order, for building a website using google my business? (list the first step at the top.)",
        "answer": []
    },
    "351": {
        "question": "you want to track conversion actions in your google ads account to better measure what matters. place the steps for setting up a conversion action in order, with the first step on top.",
        "answer": []
    },
    "352": {
        "question": "due to google analytics providing a cross-channel view of the customer journey, there\u2019ll be differences in the way conversions are measured between google analytics and google ads. which is a difference you should be aware of?",
        "answer": ["reporting freshness"]
    },
    "353": {
        "question": "aiesha is dissatisfied with the conversion rate that her ads are generating for her retail website. she wants to make some changes to improve the conversion rate. what should she do to achieve this? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["use negative keywords to add limits to her ads.", "use more specific keywords that limit the volume of clicks."]
    },
    "354": {
        "question": "brenda\u2019s promoting her business with an android app using in-app billing. she wants to measure how effectively her ads are driving in-app purchases using google ads. which two attribution partners can brenda choose between to link to her google ads in order to accomplish this? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["google firebase", "google play"]
    },
    "355": {
        "question": "an advertiser is using a global sitewide tag. where does the advertiser add a phone snippet on a website to use google forwarding numbers in a google ads campaign?",
        "answer": ["between the tags of a web page, right after the global site tag."]
    },
    "356": {
        "question": "a primary benefit of google my business is what it can tell you about how customers behave when they visit your listing. which google my business feature can you use to follow these interactions?",
        "answer": ["google my business insights"]
    },
    "357": {
        "question": "widgetco wants to increase the total amount of money they make after expenses. they\u2019re unable to change their internal costs. which factor can wedgetco lower to drive higher volume and increase the money they make after expenses?",
        "answer": ["sale price"]
    },
    "358": {
        "question": "a customer is receptive to an upsell during a product purchase. which part of the customer journey has been exhibited?",
        "answer": ["loyalty"]
    },
    "359": {
        "question": "you\u2019re reviewing the campaigns report in your google ads account to find out how effective your current ad campaign is. you\u2019re particularly interested in finding out how many people clicked each ad, even if the click didn\u2019t result in a sale. in which two columns of the campaign report will you see these metrics? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["view-through conversions", "all conversions"]
    },
    "360": {
        "question": "kyler\u2019s using conversion tracking tags to gain insight into how effectively his ads are converting customer transactions for his online store. but he notices that conversions aren\u2019t functioning. what can help him troubleshoot this issue?",
        "answer": ["google tag assistant"]
    },
    "361": {
        "question": "your online store is using firebase as its sdk for its mobile app. the app integrates with your website. you\u2019re also using google ads to manage your marketing efforts. you want to automatically import conversions into google analytics for firebase. which action will accomplish this?",
        "answer": ["make google firebase your attribution provider."]
    },
    "362": {
        "question": "brenda is compiling a list of definable metrics and key performance indicators (kpi) that will be used to evaluate the final success of her google ad campaign. which two statements can guide her as she creates a kpi? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["a kpi is clear, measurable, and has a defined time frame.", "by definition, a kpi is a measurement of success."]
    },
    "363": {
        "question": "ansel is planning a google ads campaign for his new plumbing client. he knows the client\u2019s top priority is new contact form submissions. his client is also interested in measuring newsletter subscriptions. which two conversion actions can ansel measure to showcase the campaign\u2019s results in the client\u2019s two areas of interest? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["leads", "sign-ups"]
    },
    "364": {
        "question": "you\u2019re setting up website call conversion tracking for your business, using google ads. if you don\u2019t want to manually edit your store\u2019s website code, what must you do?",
        "answer": ["create a phone snippet to replace your store\u2019s number with a google forwarding number."]
    },
    "365": {
        "question": "jared handles marketing for a chain of restaurants that feature high-end bars. he added a bar and its restaurant as separate locations in his bulk upload, even though they share an address. both were disapproved. what caused the disapproval?",
        "answer": ["multiple locations can\u2019t be uploaded at the same physical address."]
    },
    "366": {
        "question": "what\u2019s the minimum number of locations you can bulk upload to google my business?",
        "answer": ["10"]
    },
    "367": {
        "question": "your google my business listing can help customers reach you in a variety of ways. customers can use a listed address to visit your location. they can also use a phone number to place a call. which other method, if properly set up, can customers use to contact your business?",
        "answer": ["google my business messaging allows customers to text directly from yourlisting."]
    },
    "368": {
        "question": "what are two benefits of selecting google firebase as your attribution partner in google ads? (choose two.)",
        "answer": [" you can import conversions, adding any additional code to enable automatically collected events.", " you can use audiences created in firebase for conversion tracking and remarketing in google"]
    },
    "369": {
        "question": "what tag allows you to tell google ads which specific customer actions should be tracked as a conversion?",
        "answer": ["an event tag"]
    },
    "370": {
        "question": "you\u2019re working in your google ads account and set up offline conversions. you need to download the template for \u201cconversions from clicks.\u201d which two file types are supported by conversion templates? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["google sheets", "csv"]
    },
    "371": {
        "question": "felix launched both a google search ad campaign and a google display ad campaign to drive sales of tools on his home improvement website. he reviewed his sales data after two weeks and noticed his search ad campaign is the most successful. which optimization type should felix use if he wants to use bidding or targeting to acquire more customers?",
        "answer": ["channel"]
    },
    "372": {
        "question": "google my business gives businesses a variety of ways to promote their goods and services to users online. what are the key benefits of google my business?",
        "answer": ["share information with customers, manage multiple listings together, engage with customers, and get insights on customer behavior."]
    },
    "373": {
        "question": "creating a call conversion in google ads and adding a phone snippet to a web page allows advertisers to use a google forwarding number. what does this number allow you to monitor?",
        "answer": ["the length of each call and time it took place."]
    },
    "374": {
        "question": "felix launched a google search ad campaign to drive sales of tools on his home improvement website. after reviewing sales data from the first week, felix notices higher sales from ads with a specific picture of his tools. he changes the pictures of his other ads to be similar to the successful ads. which type of channel optimization is felix using to drive higher tool sales?",
        "answer": ["creative"]
    },
    "375": {
        "question": "cliff is a marketing manager who received a series of ads from his creative team. he wants to compare data between those ads using a/b testing. which type of ads will cliff compare?",
        "answer": ["ads used in identical ways, on the same channels, and directed at the same audience."]
    },
    "376": {
        "question": "heather\u2019s using google ads to promote her online olive-oil business. she\u2019s setting up a conversion action to measure how effectively her ad campaign is increasing sales on her website. which category of conversion action should heather select as part of the setup?",
        "answer": ["purchase"]
    },
    "377": {
        "question": "how is credit dynamically attributed to each touch-point in data-driven attribution?",
        "answer": ["it algorithmically evaluates individual customer paths to assign credit."]
    },
    "378": {
        "question": "to avoid double counting, what will have to be removed from a website page prior to the addition of an event tag?",
        "answer": ["any legacy conversion tag"]
    },
    "379": {
        "question": "which method should be used to promote awareness to customers?",
        "answer": ["ads with generic search terms"]
    },
    "380": {
        "question": "if you\u2019re interested in tracking conversions in your google ads campaigns and have google analytics already installed, there\u2019ll be differences in the conversion data reported by the two systems. what are two of these differences? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["differences in conversion counts", "differences in attribution"]
    },
    "381": {
        "question": "you\u2019re serving on a marketing team for an online client, and you\u2019ve been asked to create a list of key performance indicators (kpis) to help improve the effectiveness of a current online ad campaign. what are two guiding principles that will help you create these kpis? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["kpis are quantifiable over a period of time.", "a kpi is a measurement of success."]
    },
    "382": {
        "question": "you decide to bulk upload your multiple business locations to google my business. some of the locations in your upload were disapproved. which two errors can cause this issue? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["multiple locations in one physical address", "incorrect business name"]
    },
    "383": {
        "question": "jon implemented conversion tracking tags for his website. he recently released an app as well. jon\u2019s reviewing the totals across all conversions using the campaign report in google ads, but he wants to see the conversion results specifically for app installs and first opens. how can he accomplish this?",
        "answer": ["by segmenting the data by conversion action in campaigns."]
    },
    "384": {
        "question": "madison owns a retail clothing store. her marketing consultant says that with all the technology at their disposal, customers will go back and forth across multiple channels before choosing to buy an outfit at her store. the consultant recommends that madison think about her customer\u2019s journey before they actually arrive at her store. which type of strategy is madison\u2019s marketing director suggesting to help her drive sales at her physical location?",
        "answer": []
    },
    "385": {
        "question": "tristan owns a local flower shop. his customers are already finding him online, but he\u2019s curious whether google my business can do more than just list his phone number and address. how can google my business help tristan engage his customers?",
        "answer": ["by responding to reviews."]
    },
    "386": {
        "question": "everett just finished building a website for his bus-touring company using the google my business website builder. he followed the required steps, and is eager to see his new website live on the web. after pointing the domain at his new website, how long does it usually take for the site to appear online if the site is built correctly?",
        "answer": ["it should be live on the web in only a few minutes."]
    },
    "387": {
        "question": "larry owns a dry cleaning business and would like to give his customers every opportunity to reach him. his google my business panel provides his phone number, but he knows some of his online customers would prefer to text for information. how can google my business help larry?",
        "answer": ["larry can set up messaging by adding a mobile number to google my business."]
    },
    "388": {
        "question": "you added a conversion tracking tag to a landing page on your business\u2019s website. when analyzing your purchasing data, you find duplicate conversions. what\u2019s causing the duplicates?",
        "answer": ["customers who made a purchase return to the conversion page."]
    },
    "389": {
        "question": "linda is viewing the campaign report in her google ads account after successfully implementing conversion tracking tags for her website. she sees that at least two of her ads generated over 100 view-through conversions. which two count as view-through conversions? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["someone clicking on a part of those particular ads.", "someone watching up to 30 seconds of those ads."]
    },
    "390": {
        "question": "which two statements are true about evaluating your existing ad campaigns? (choose two.) select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["measurement results should lead to actionable insights; it should inform your decision-making.", "one of the first steps you must take is to check whether the result of a specific objective exceeded or fell short of its goal."]
    },
    "391": {
        "question": "your company produces candy bars. you need a method for determining the amount of sales driven by each media channel in your advertising campaign. you want a method that considers all possible factors in those sales, such as marketing, branding consideration, the economy, competitor actions, and even the weather. which analysis technique should you use?",
        "answer": ["media mixed model"]
    },
    "392": {
        "question": "camila has an online store and is using google ads to improve her online advertising efforts. she currently has google analytics set up for her website and now wants to set up conversion tracking in google ads. what must she do in order to make conversion tracking effective?",
        "answer": ["link her google ads and analytics accounts"]
    },
    "393": {
        "question": "in google my business, where can you find the number of google my business visitors that are receiving driving directions to your location?",
        "answer": ["google my business insights"]
    },
    "394": {
        "question": "which statement is true about time-decay attribution?",
        "answer": ["it gives more credit to the touch-points closest to the conversion."]
    },
    "395": {
        "question": "how can a google my business location can be verified?",
        "answer": ["by phone, e-mail, or postcard"]
    },
    "396": {
        "question": "jamelle wants to use google ads to advertise his website. he\u2019s considering using one of the available smart bidding strategies that google offers. what are two smart bidding strategies that jamelle can use for his upcoming campaign? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["maximize conversions", "enhanced cpc"]
    },
    "397": {
        "question": "which activity might a brand manager track if the desired result is to increase awareness with the customer?",
        "answer": ["brand recall"]
    },
    "398": {
        "question": "susan\u2019s created a gaming app, which she\u2019s promoting on google ads. she wants to track first opens of the gaming app. what must she do first, before she can begin tracking opens of her app?",
        "answer": ["link her firebase and google ads account."]
    },
    "399": {
        "question": "you\u2019ve set up conversion actions for your online retail site. now you want to set up conversion tracking tags to gain some deeper insights into how people engage with your ads. match the required tagging action with the corresponding conversion measurement.",
        "answer": []
    },
    "400": {
        "question": "carlos has a physical store and doesn\u2019t have the ability to sell his products online. but he still advertises online and wants to measure how effective his online ads are in driving new customers in-store and generating new sales. what is the best way for carlos to achieve this within google ads?",
        "answer": ["import offline conversions."]
    },
    "401": {
        "question": "match each product available in google marketing platform for enterprise with its description.",
        "answer": []
    },
    "402": {
        "question": "brad wants to link his firebase account to his google ads account for his e-commerce app. what are the required minimum permissions for brad\u2019s google account to be able to do this?",
        "answer": ["in firebase, the account needs to be an owner on the project you want to link."]
    },
    "403": {
        "question": "linking a client\u2019s google my business with google ads allows for the creation of location extensions. which statement is true about location extensions?",
        "answer": ["location extensions add an address, a link to see the business on google maps, or the distance a user is from the location to campaign ads."]
    },
    "404": {
        "question": "each google my business location has a unique id that applies changes to the right listing. what\u2019s the name of this unique id?",
        "answer": ["store code"]
    },
    "405": {
        "question": "in a survey, a customer shows a strong preference for one brand over another. which general metric does this behavior fall under?",
        "answer": ["consideration"]
    },
    "406": {
        "question": "cory owns a custom purse-design business. he launched an advertising campaign featuring purses made of environmentally friendly materials. he\u2019s followed his customers through their entire journeys. what\u2019s cory\u2019s final aim when engaging customers in their journey?",
        "answer": ["to build brand loyalty"]
    },
    "407": {
        "question": "what\u2019s the best indicator that a campaign is increasing customer loyalty?",
        "answer": ["customer referrals"]
    },
    "408": {
        "question": "once you\u2019ve established conversion actions in your google ads account, you\u2019ll be provided with a conversion tracking tag. what should you do with this snippet of code to successfully track conversion actions?",
        "answer": ["add the conversion tag to your website or app."]
    },
    "409": {
        "question": "which attribution type algorithmically evaluates individual customer paths?",
        "answer": ["data-driven"]
    },
    "410": {
        "question": "senior executives at a global manufacturing company are determining thekey performance indicators they\u2019ll use to judge how effective their online video advertising campaigns will be on google ads. what guidelines are they creating?",
        "answer": ["campaign metrics"]
    },
    "411": {
        "question": "kellie wants to buy an expensive purse from a local accessory store. as a savvy consumer, kellie wants to find an exact brand at the right price. which strategy will help an accessory store engage kellie throughout her customer journey, from the time she begins research to the time she purchases the purse?",
        "answer": ["an online-to-offline strategy"]
    },
    "412": {
        "question": "marisol owns a busy yoga studio popular with local college communities. her customers call daily to check on class times, availability, and pricing, which takes too much of her staff\u2019s time. marisol would love to use google my business to provide the answers these customers need, without requiring her staff to take calls. which feature of google my business could marisol use to accomplish this?",
        "answer": ["google my business messaging lets her send a quick text that answers her customers\u2019 questions."]
    },
    "413": {
        "question": "why is it difficult, or maybe impossible, to calculate a total increase in brand awareness from a campaign spanning multiple media channels?",
        "answer": ["multiple media channels may use different tools to measure brand lift."]
    },
    "414": {
        "question": "tara knows google my business is a great way to share information and engage her customers online. but she\u2019s worried because she has multiple locations, and management may be too difficult. how does google my business address tara\u2019s concern?",
        "answer": ["tara can manage multiple google my business listings together."]
    },
    "415": {
        "question": "tom is a web developer who also runs an online store. he uses google ads. he wants to integrate conversion tracking on his site with the updated google ads conversion tracking tag (gtag.js). what must he do in order integrate conversion tracking?",
        "answer": ["input the tag code between the tags of each of web page."]
    },
    "416": {
        "question": "if you\u2019ve set up conversion actions in google ads and google analytics, you\u2019ll notice differences in the way this data is calculated between the two platforms. what\u2019s one of these differences?",
        "answer": ["the date of transaction"]
    },
    "417": {
        "question": "mary\u2019s a marketing manager for a nationwide vegan restaurant chain. she\u2019s considering which digital channel she should use to advertise her restaurant\u2019s new menu upgrades to people who prefer vegan food. which two digital channels could mary use to reach her audience? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["video", "e-mail"]
    },
    "418": {
        "question": "felix launched both a google video ad campaign and a google shopping ad campaign to drive sales of lumber on his home improvement website. he reviews his conversion data after two weeks and notices his video ads campaign seem to be assisting in driving higher lumber sales. he moves more of his budget to the video ads campaign. which type of optimization has felix used to drive higher lumber sales?",
        "answer": ["media mix optimization"]
    },
    "419": {
        "question": "you want to complete conversion tracking setup on your business website with google ads. you\u2019ve already implemented a global sitewide tag. your next step is to create event tags, which must be placed in the correct section of your web pages to properly function. where\u2019s the event tag implemented on a web page?",
        "answer": ["between the tags of your website page, right after the global site tag."]
    },
    "420": {
        "question": "match each report with its description.",
        "answer": []
    },
    "421": {
        "question": "brianna has a physical store that she\u2019s successfully managed for 10 years. her products aren\u2019t designed to sell and ship online. she recently created an online website and app to advertise her business. now she\u2019s interested in using google ads to create an ad campaign and measure its effectiveness. how will offline conversion tracking help brianna?",
        "answer": ["brianna can measure offline sales initiated from an ad click."]
    },
    "422": {
        "question": "sara\u2019s a marketing executive for an online clothing retailer. she\u2019s focused on data-driven measurement to drive sales of her company\u2019s clothing lines. she turned to google\u2019s automated machine learning to help her company gain a competitive advantage in the marketplace. what does sara do to succeed at automation?",
        "answer": []
    },
    "423": {
        "question": "vijay needs to design a website for his taxi company. he\u2019s considering using the google my business website builder. his biggest concern is whether he can produce a site capable of serving his customers on mobile phones and tablets. how does the google my business website builder address this concern?",
        "answer": ["google my business website builder will format the site to deliver on any device."]
    },
    "424": {
        "question": "a brand manager wants to show the value of his advertising by demonstrating the return on ad investment. what\u2019s his marketing objective?",
        "answer": ["purchase"]
    },
    "425": {
        "question": "levi\u2019s an experienced marketing strategist for a software company that sells a learning platform to public schools. he developed healthy individual measurement habits that drive his success in constantly evolving his company\u2019s marketing strategies to the schools\u2019 changing needs. what are two habits levi developed to help him evaluate and adapt his marketing strategies? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["he starts his day by looking at how well he\u2019s doing on his company\u2019s key performance indicators.", "he values what his coworkers think and encourages them to give their opinions in his marketing meetings."]
    },
    "426": {
        "question": "heather created kpis (key performance indicators) for her shoe company. she\u2019s using metrics to determine whether or not those kpis have been met. using the dropdown menu, select whether each option is one of heather\u2019s kpis or a metric.",
        "answer": []
    },
    "427": {
        "question": "which statement describes rules-based attribution?",
        "answer": ["it applies static logic to assign a value to each touch-point."]
    },
    "428": {
        "question": "david owns a retail business that just implemented a web app to supplement sales. he needs to choose an attribution partner to integrate the app for in-app conversion tracking. which two are available attribution providers? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["google firebase", "google play"]
    },
    "429": {
        "question": "you\u2019d like to modify your current bidding strategy to increase the conversion rate of your ads. match each bidding strategy with its description.",
        "answer": []
    },
    "430": {
        "question": "you\u2019ve been hired as a consultant to help an online store owner. you need to complete the implementation of conversion tracking tags into their website. what are two ways that google tag assistant can help you with this task? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["it tells you which tags are on each web page.", "it provides reasons why tags aren\u2019t working."]
    },
    "431": {
        "question": "peter has a website that promotes his local vacation rental site. he uses google ads to manage his advertising campaign. he\u2019s cross-referencing his purchase conversions with his backend crm, and the data isn\u2019t matching up. what\u2019s an attributed reason for this discrepancy?",
        "answer": ["conversion tracking is generating duplicate conversions."]
    },
    "432": {
        "question": "julie is trying to determine why there are such dynamic fluctuations in the conversion volume of her online website in the past three months. she begins investigating possible causes for the fluctuations. what are two recommended actions she can take in her investigation? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["view the time lag report to better understand her visitor\u2019s conversion path.", "review the full history of her account changes over the specific date selected, as ad changes might affect conversions."]
    },
    "433": {
        "question": "conversion measurement is an excellent way for businesses to understand how users are engaging with their brand. match each conversion action to a relevant example of a business need.",
        "answer": []
    },
    "434": {
        "question": "kathy released a gaming app and needs to set up conversion tracking for first opens of the app. to do this, she linked her firebase project with google ads. which access permission did her google account need for her to do this?",
        "answer": ["administrative access in google ads"]
    },
    "435": {
        "question": "raven has successfully added her location to google my business. she knows she has options for verification, including use of a phone call or e-mail. how else can she verify her location?",
        "answer": ["with a postcard delivered by mail."]
    },
    "436": {
        "question": "rodney\u2019s trying to set up offline tracking using his google ads account. he downloaded the conversion template he wants to use. he adds the appropriate offline data and modifies it. when he tries to upload the template, the import process fails. what will cause the import process to fail?",
        "answer": ["the gclid field\u2019s been removed from the conversion template."]
    },
    "437": {
        "question": "tom\u2019s setting up website call conversion tracking for his business\u2019s website, using google ads. place the steps required for the setup in the correct order. (the first step is on top.)",
        "answer": []
    },
    "438": {
        "question": "you want to set firebase as your attribution partner in google ads in order to track first opens for your online store app. what\u2019s the first step you must implement in order to accomplish this?",
        "answer": ["link your firebase project to your google ads account."]
    },
    "439": {
        "question": "which feature should you use to find information regarding specific actions visitors have taken on your google my business listing over a given period of time?",
        "answer": ["google my business insights"]
    },
    "440": {
        "question": "gail is a marketing manager who received a series of ads from her creative team. she wants to improve her ad content by using a/b testing. which type of ads will gail compare?",
        "answer": ["ads used in identical ways, on the same channels, and directed at the same audience."]
    },
    "441": {
        "question": "bill owns a company called wild bill\u2019s bracelets that sells custom jewelry. he launched a search campaign to drive sales of his custom-made bracelets on his website. how can bill create effective messages that drive more customers to purchase his jewelry?",
        "answer": ["he can use brand-specific search terms."]
    },
    "442": {
        "question": "if you have ten or more locations, you can bulk upload those locations to google my business using a spreadsheet that contains five important fields. match the fields to their descriptions.",
        "answer": []
    },
    "443": {
        "question": "which google measurement product is designed for brick-and-mortar retailers that collect shopper purchase data in a customer relationship management system?",
        "answer": ["store sales direct"]
    },
    "444": {
        "question": "tom\u2019s using google ads to promote his bicycle store. he\u2019s created an android app and needs to measure how effectively the current ad campaign is driving purchases how can tom accomplish this?",
        "answer": ["by setting up a conversion action for in-app purchases."]
    },
    "445": {
        "question": "olyana works at a digital marketing agency. she\u2019d like to use google forwarding numbers to track the duration of calls originating from one of her client\u2019s campaigns. she created a conversion action for call conversions inside google ads, which produced a tag for her to download. what is this tag called?",
        "answer": ["a phone snippet"]
    },
    "446": {
        "question": "which analysis technique is particularly useful for companies that invest a significant amount of their media budget in offline media channels or companies that sell predominantly through local stores?",
        "answer": ["media mix model"]
    },
    "447": {
        "question": "match each product available in the google marketing platform small business version with its description.",
        "answer": []
    },
    "448": {
        "question": "google my business helps businesses engage their customers in the moments that matter most. what are two ways google my business accomplishes this? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["communicates with customers.", "responds to reviews."]
    },
    "449": {
        "question": "google my business verification has specific requirements for approval: the business name must be exactly as it appears in real life, and the business can\u2019t have multiple locations in one physical address. what\u2019s the third potential reason for disapproval in the verification process?",
        "answer": ["location isn\u2019t yet open."]
    },
    "450": {
        "question": "anthony has a dog-walking business that he manages online, and he\u2019s adopted google ads to drive more traffic to his website. he\u2019s one month into his first campaign on google ads, now reviewing his conversion data to determine how his ads are performing. he sees that his view-through conversions (vtcs) are low. he\u2019s not sure what vtcs are and what this data means knowing which two facts about vtcs would help anthony better understand his conversion data? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["a view is counted if a person watches an ad for up to 30 seconds or clicks on a part of the ad.", "vtcs are conversions that are recorded when users view (but don\u2019t interact with) an ad and then later convert."]
    },
    "451": {
        "question": "as the director of advertising for a software company, susan\u2019s considering her customers\u2019 journeys. what\u2019s the first step her potential customers will take?",
        "answer": ["view an online advertisement"]
    },
    "452": {
        "question": "antonio runs an online retail site and wants to set up a sitewide tag to measure online conversions for his future google ad campaigns. he\u2019s already set up conversion actions and has google tag manager managing tags on his site. which tag type should he choose to complete this process?",
        "answer": ["conversion linker"]
    },
    "453": {
        "question": "brenda implemented conversion tracking tags for her website. she\u2019s reviewing the total conversions across her ads, using the campaigns report. she\u2019d like to see the total for each conversion type. how can she accomplish this?",
        "answer": ["by segmenting the data by conversion action."]
    },
    "454": {
        "question": "an extra line is included within an ad when location extensions are added to a google ad campaign. all it takes is linking google my business with a google ads account. what can users see when an ad with location extensions is displayed?",
        "answer": ["an address, a link to see the business on google maps, or specific distance to location"]
    },
    "455": {
        "question": "joshua is creating a new google ads campaign and wants to track specific actions customers take on his website. he knows that a global site tag has been implemented on the site, making the use of event tags a possibility. which two types of event tags can joshua create? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["page load", "click"]
    },
    "456": {
        "question": "a clothing company wants to entice consumers to pay more for their products. to do this, the company launches an advertising campaign to position themselves as a luxury brand. which factor are they trying to improve?",
        "answer": ["demand"]
    },
    "457": {
        "question": "what can the performance planner recommend?",
        "answer": ["campaign-level target cpa (cost-per-acquisition)"]
    },
    "458": {
        "question": "alex has started a google search campaign designed to promote his online motorcycle accessories store\u2026",
        "answer": ["by showing his ad to people searching for related information about helmets."]
    },
    "459": {
        "question": "using the performance planner on a monthly basis allows you to optimize which two aspects of an account?",
        "answer": ["bids", "budgets"]
    },
    "460": {
        "question": "samira has been tasked with increasing the relevance of her company\u2019s ads. she has been told that she can\u2026",
        "answer": ["up to 15 headlines"]
    },
    "461": {
        "question": "which is required for an ad to be served to a user?",
        "answer": ["the keywords must be relevant to the search term."]
    },
    "462": {
        "question": "hank wants to use a \u201cmaximize conversions\u201d campaign with the performance planner. which recommendation\u2026",
        "answer": ["a recommended average daily budget"]
    },
    "463": {
        "question": "what content could be used for a structured snippet extension?",
        "answer": ["berlin, london, paris, singapore"]
    },
    "464": {
        "question": "you want to increase the relevance of a google search ad so it\u2019s more meaningful to potential customers\u2026",
        "answer": ["selecting distinct geographic areas.", "selecting only relevant languages in campaign setup."]
    },
    "465": {
        "question": "bob\u2019s electronics company has quite a buzz around a new television they\u2019re launching, called ultraview1000\u2026",
        "answer": ["bob\u2019s ad will appear if search terms contain at least all three of the keywords orvariations of those terms."]
    },
    "466": {
        "question": "what does adding callout extensions to your google search ads enable you to do?",
        "answer": ["highlight information about value-adding attributes of your business, products, orservices."]
    },
    "467": {
        "question": "while managing a successful google ads campaign, why would you choose automated bidding instead of manual\u2026",
        "answer": ["because given the dynamic nature of google\u2019s auctions, the appropriate bid can often be a moving target that is challenging to reach at scale when using manual bidding"]
    },
    "468": {
        "question": "what\u2019s an example of an effective callout extension?",
        "answer": ["free returns"]
    },
    "469": {
        "question": "google ads reviews saved text ads to ensure they meet advertising policies before being shown to users\u2026",
        "answer": ["content and formatting."]
    },
    "470": {
        "question": "your google search ads optimization score is calculated by an algorithm that looks across key aspects of\u2026",
        "answer": []
    },
    "471": {
        "question": "what are two ways dynamic search ads brings value to an advertising campaign?",
        "answer": ["it creates new ads automatically.", "it finds traffic an advertiser might miss."]
    },
    "472": {
        "question": "why is using the performance targets feature after utilizing the performance planner recommended?",
        "answer": ["this practice allows you to monitor targets set in the performance planner and to receive alerts and recommendations when a campaign is not on track."]
    },
    "473": {
        "question": "trina is using automated bidding as part of her google ads search bidding strategy. why might she prefer\u2026",
        "answer": ["machine learning helps her set the appropriate bid for each and every auction."]
    },
    "474": {
        "question": "jim has created a google search ad with a bid of $5. two other advertisers in an auction have bids of $2.50\u2026",
        "answer": ["$2.51"]
    },
    "475": {
        "question": "wendy is setting up a customer match strategy to reach a list of prospective customers. what must she provide?",
        "answer": ["customer relationship management data"]
    },
    "476": {
        "question": "how can performance planner serve your business?",
        "answer": ["by optimizing your ad budget for maximum growth"]
    },
    "477": {
        "question": "mary wants to run a text ad on the google search network. she\u2019s new to text ads and needs to start with the\u2026",
        "answer": ["headline, url, description"]
    },
    "478": {
        "question": "singh\u2019s marketing company has created an enticing ad that receives many clicks. what effect will the ad\u2026",
        "answer": ["the higher expected click-through rate will lead to a higher ad rank."]
    },
    "479": {
        "question": "steven is an advertising executive at a large auto parts company. he uses his google ads recommendations\u2026",
        "answer": ["apply recommendations across multiple layers of his advertising strategy"]
    },
    "480": {
        "question": "what is one way that performance planner helps businesses increase sales?",
        "answer": ["by maximizing the number of conversions for a spend scenario"]
    },
    "481": {
        "question": "what does layering an affinity audience with a broad keyword targeting campaign help you do?",
        "answer": ["ensure your ads are only seen by people who have demonstrated a qualified interestin your service and/or product(s)"]
    },
    "482": {
        "question": "what can the performance planner assist you with?",
        "answer": ["to improve return on investment so you can drive more conversions within your target cpa(cost-per-acquisition)"]
    },
    "483": {
        "question": "how is using non-last-click attribution conversions useful for performance planner forecasts?",
        "answer": ["to allocate budgets that drive incremental conversions"]
    },
    "484": {
        "question": "what are two main benefits of using search audience solutions? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["making the right bids when certain groups of people are searching for your product or services", "reaching different audience segments with unique messaging that is highly relevant to them"]
    },
    "485": {
        "question": "jerry\u2019s managing a google search campaign and would like to improve the position in which his ads appear\u2026",
        "answer": ["create a helpful, relevant landing page for the ad."]
    },
    "486": {
        "question": "lisa sells kitchen furniture through her website. while her sales are stable, she\u2019s concerned that they\u2019re\u2026",
        "answer": ["her business will have a competitive presence with similar businesses during searches."]
    },
    "487": {
        "question": "ginger\u2019s working on creating her first google search ad. she wants to create an inviting and relevant ad,\u2026",
        "answer": ["has a relevant headline", "includes a current promotion"]
    },
    "488": {
        "question": "ad extensions assist in providing users with which two things they want from their search experience?",
        "answer": ["relevant information", "information based on their moment"]
    },
    "489": {
        "question": "what\u2019s a key objective in delivering ad extensions?",
        "answer": ["providing the right users with the right information at the right moment."]
    },
    "490": {
        "question": "as an advertiser, creating your first text ad in google ads is a simple five\u2026",
        "answer": ["first step:", "second step:", "third step:", "fourth step:", "fifth step: "]
    },
    "491": {
        "question": "yan is working on a remarketing list for search ads campaign. which user could be added to a valid remarket\u2026",
        "answer": ["someone who has added items to a shopping basket on his company\u2019s website but thenabandoned it"]
    },
    "492": {
        "question": "bob\u2019s electronics company is launching a new television called ultraview1000. bob decides to use broad\u2026",
        "answer": ["bob\u2019s ad will appear if search terms contain some variation of his keyword, such as \u201ctv.\u201d"]
    },
    "493": {
        "question": "trevor owns a manufacturing business that makes specialized hiking and rock-climbing gear. he\u2019s a small\u2026",
        "answer": ["display"]
    },
    "494": {
        "question": "automated bidding does the heavy lifting for advertisers on google ads. what does automated bidding use to\u2026",
        "answer": ["machine learning"]
    },
    "495": {
        "question": "what\u2019s the primary benefit of using structured snippet extensions in your ads?",
        "answer": ["gives users specific information about what you\u2019re offering, before they visit your website."]
    },
    "496": {
        "question": "an advertising executive takes over a google search ads campaign. on his google ads recommendations page he\u2026",
        "answer": ["<a>the campaign could be improved by 60% if the listed recommendations are followed</a>."]
    },
    "497": {
        "question": "what two ad extension types can also be served as automated ad extensions? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["sitelink extension", "callout extension"]
    },
    "498": {
        "question": "rebecca is a marketing executive at an airline company. she has been asked to plan her company\u2019s online\u2026",
        "answer": ["performance planner forecasting is powered by billions of google searches conducted eachweek.", "performance planner leverages machine learning for forecasting."]
    },
    "499": {
        "question": "mario is working on a text ad that will run on the google search network. he filled in each component with\u2026",
        "answer": ["the description component"]
    },
    "500": {
        "question": "bernadette\u2019s in charge of marketing a new product in a highly competitive segment. she\u2019s planning to launch\u2026",
        "answer": []
    },
    "501": {
        "question": "you\u2019ve seen great results from your google search campaigns when using remarketing lists for search ads\u2026",
        "answer": ["use similar audiences to find new visitors for your site"]
    },
    "502": {
        "question": "google ads was constructed around three core principles, focused on helping businesses reach their online\u2026",
        "answer": ["control and results"]
    },
    "503": {
        "question": "carlton runs an adventure excursion company in south america. he\u2019d like to increase the number of people\u2026",
        "answer": ["researching south american holiday destinations online."]
    },
    "504": {
        "question": "your company provides home-maintenance services, and you want to reach more potential customers\u2026",
        "answer": ["you can set your own budget and can change it at any time."]
    },
    "505": {
        "question": "priya only has $500 a month to spend on her campaign, but she needs to drive as many potential customers as\u2026",
        "answer": ["maximize clicks"]
    },
    "506": {
        "question": "it is 10 a.m. and you are sitting in a train station in london, looking through your calendar on your tablet.",
        "answer": []
    },
    "507": {
        "question": "match each ad extension with the benefit it brings to a user\u2019s ad experience.",
        "answer": []
    },
    "508": {
        "question": "what are two ways that performance planner can help reveal the possibilities across all your google ads\u2026",
        "answer": ["validation", "simulation"]
    },
    "509": {
        "question": "maria has been told that she should use the performance planner on a monthly basis. why should she do so?",
        "answer": ["to react to ever-changing external factors"]
    },
    "510": {
        "question": "francis wants to increase his google ads skills and optimize results for his clients. what two best practices\u2026",
        "answer": ["include three to five ads, and at least three extensions in each ad group.", "optimize the campaign\u2019s ad rotation for clicks or conversion actions."]
    },
    "511": {
        "question": "john\u2019s plumbing prides itself on excellent customer service, especially during after-hours service calls\u2026",
        "answer": ["ad scheduling"]
    },
    "512": {
        "question": "helen\u2019s heating and air (hha) wants to encourage interest in their new smart refrigerators. they know that\u2026",
        "answer": ["smart refrigerator reviews", "energy-efficient fridge"]
    },
    "513": {
        "question": "you are working to improve the quality score of a google search ad by increasing your ectr. your goal is to\u2026",
        "answer": ["adding more specifics to the ad."]
    },
    "514": {
        "question": "yan wants to attract customers specifically searching on google for time-b-gone, his company\u2019s unique office\u2026",
        "answer": ["landing pages from standard ad groups"]
    },
    "515": {
        "question": "when visibility is the campaign goal, which bidding strategy should an advertiser choose?",
        "answer": ["target impression share"]
    },
    "516": {
        "question": "samira recently opened an online potted plant store and needs to promote it. she chose google ads because\u2026",
        "answer": ["shopping campaigns, which promote her products by giving consumers detailed informationabout what she\u2019s selling before they click her ad."]
    },
    "517": {
        "question": "a golf enthusiast regularly watches instructional videos about golf, has recently searched for the best golf\u2026",
        "answer": ["affinity audience"]
    },
    "518": {
        "question": "swee yin\u2019s fashion-apparel department store runs a popular biannual sale on men\u2019s hats, with large discounts and surprise bonus items. she wants to tailor her google search campaign to highlight this sale. how can google search campaigns be tailored to promote her company\u2019s sales event?",
        "answer": []
    },
    "519": {
        "question": "karen has evaluated her google search ads campaign\u2019s optimization score after noticing that the campaign\u2019s\u2026",
        "answer": ["it will improve upon acceptance."]
    },
    "520": {
        "question": "you\u2019ve been tasked with marketing a new line of plumbing services, but you have a set budget you can\u2019t exceed.",
        "answer": ["google ads gives you control over your budget."]
    },
    "521": {
        "question": "john\u2019s company makes a great product and customers are happy with their purchases. unfortunately, few\u2026",
        "answer": ["with multiple headline and description options, responsive ads can compete in more auctions for a wider range of search terms.", "with lower costs-per-click, advertisers using responsive ads can afford to be in more daily auctions."]
    },
    "522": {
        "question": "carrie owns a gardening store and uses a website to promote all the products she sells. a user saw a google\u2026",
        "answer": ["searching for related gardening information."]
    },
    "523": {
        "question": "rashid wants to raise awareness of his brand and build campaigns focused on branded terms. he doesn\u2019t have\u2026",
        "answer": ["target impression share"]
    },
    "524": {
        "question": "what search network text ad component provides up to three fields of 30 characters each?",
        "answer": ["the headline component"]
    },
    "525": {
        "question": "silly sayings is seeing a lot of website traffic, but the company wants to generate more qualified leads\u2026",
        "answer": ["by providing users with relevant information up-front."]
    },
    "526": {
        "question": "brian manages his company\u2019s google search ads campaign. he regularly reviews the optimization score to make\u2026",
        "answer": ["key aspects of his accounts, including statistics, settings, and industry trends"]
    },
    "527": {
        "question": "you\u2019d like to improve an ad\u2019s perceived quality during an ad auction. what aspect of the ad will be most\u2026",
        "answer": ["improving the navigability of the landing page."]
    },
    "528": {
        "question": "reggie manages the online marketing campaigns for a vitamin and supplement store. he launched a\u2026",
        "answer": ["getting more customers to learn about his products."]
    },
    "529": {
        "question": "your google search text ad has three main components. the first is a headline, and the second is a description",
        "answer": ["the url displaying your website address."]
    },
    "530": {
        "question": "match these search audience solutions with the benefits they can bring to",
        "answer": []
    },
    "531": {
        "question": "you\u2019re working on a google search ad that\u2019s not performing as expected. you specifically want more users to\u2026",
        "answer": ["changing the call-to-action message of the ad."]
    },
    "532": {
        "question": "what is the minimum number of users a remarketing list must have before being used with a remarketing\u2026",
        "answer": ["1,000 users"]
    },
    "533": {
        "question": "jimmy sells televisions on his website. he notices he\u2019s getting traffic from searches for a brand he\u2026",
        "answer": ["his ads won\u2019t be shown to users searching for the uncarried brand."]
    },
    "534": {
        "question": "which statement is true about serving relevant ad extensions?",
        "answer": ["they encourage users to make more informed decisions and take action."]
    },
    "535": {
        "question": "siona needs to make sure her ads are getting a minimum number of impressions on the top of the page\u2026",
        "answer": ["target impression share"]
    },
    "536": {
        "question": "clara is an advertising director who has been tasked with optimizing her company\u2019s google search campaign\u2026",
        "answer": ["to find how close her campaign is from potential ideal results"]
    },
    "537": {
        "question": "what does performance planner automatically do?",
        "answer": ["forecasts how your current campaigns will perform in the future"]
    },
    "538": {
        "question": "a water-sports company specializes in custom-made watercrafts and accessories. their marketing manager\u2026",
        "answer": ["a green boat paddle", "travel on a paddle ship"]
    },
    "539": {
        "question": "what is a main benefit of using search audience solutions?",
        "answer": ["they can help send the right message to the right customer with the right bid."]
    },
    "540": {
        "question": "what\u2019s the maximum number of ad extensions that can show for a particular query or device at any given time?",
        "answer": ["4"]
    },
    "541": {
        "question": "your client, vince\u2019s veggies, wants to increase downloads of their popular recipe printouts. you suggest they create ad groups based on the cooking categories that appear on their website. what will they need to create in their first google search ad group? (choose two.)",
        "answer": ["keyword list", "default bid amount"]
    },
    "542": {
        "question": "google ads was designed to help businesses achieve online success. to accomplish this, google ads was built\u2026",
        "answer": ["relevance, control, and results"]
    },
    "543": {
        "question": "asam is learning about google ads search. he wants to know why a marketer might use callout extensions. for which activity are callout extensions beneficial?",
        "answer": ["highlight key information and unique selling points of a business"]
    },
    "544": {
        "question": "when creating an ad, how does greg know what it will look like to his potential customers?",
        "answer": ["as he types in his url, headline, and description, a preview of the mobile and desktop versions of his ad will appear."]
    },
    "545": {
        "question": "you want to improve the relevance of an ad with a particular set of keywords. the goal is to increase the\u2026",
        "answer": ["adding more negative keywords."]
    },
    "546": {
        "question": "jennifer\u2019s company wants to increase online sales of a featured product by connecting with users who are\u2026",
        "answer": ["her ads may appear when a user is likely to be interested in her product."]
    },
    "547": {
        "question": "with similar audiences, which google product is included when finding new people with similar profiles?",
        "answer": ["youtube"]
    },
    "548": {
        "question": "marco owns a company that installs smart-home accessories. his employees recently completed specialized\u2026",
        "answer": ["his ad may appear when people research similar installation options."]
    },
    "549": {
        "question": "you\u2019re trying to improve an ad\u2019s perceived quality so it performs better during an ad auction.",
        "answer": ["raising the bid amount."]
    },
    "550": {
        "question": "sam\u2019s new to google search ads and worries he may not have the skills or time to run a successful ad campaign.",
        "answer": ["machine learning helps automatically find new keywords.", "destination urls are automatically kept up-to-date."]
    },
    "551": {
        "question": "which user type would the google ads system closely match as an affinity audience",
        "answer": ["someone who has demonstrated a qualified interest in movies"]
    },
    "552": {
        "question": "in-market audiences allow the opportunity to specifically identify what kind of user?",
        "answer": []
    },
    "553": {
        "question": "michael built a high-quality ad with an excellent keyword list. he\u2019s disappointed the ad isn\u2019t being shown\u2026",
        "answer": ["his bid for the ad is too low."]
    },
    "554": {
        "question": "what is the difference between programmatic guaranteed deals and preferred deals?",
        "answer": ["programmatic guaranteed deals have required minimum spend"]
    },
    "555": {
        "question": "what step should be taken to configure a programmatic guaranteed deal once negotiations are complete?",
        "answer": ["in my inventory, find the deal and select configure"]
    },
    "556": {
        "question": "at what levels can pacing be set?",
        "answer": ["insertion order and line item"]
    },
    "557": {
        "question": "when targeting a private deal with a news publisher that constantly refreshes the text on the page, which targeting should be avoided?",
        "answer": ["keyword"]
    },
    "558": {
        "question": "where can an advertiser set their campaign goal?",
        "answer": ["campaign settings"]
    },
    "559": {
        "question": "what step should be taken to view performance data for targeted audience segments?",
        "answer": ["generate an audience performance report and select \u201cinclude only targeted audience lists\u201d"]
    },
    "560": {
        "question": "how can a creative be submitted for audit after it\u2019s been rejected and fixed?",
        "answer": ["select the creative and select \u201cactivate\u201d"]
    },
    "561": {
        "question": "when users make changes to a line item or insertion order, where are those changes displayed?",
        "answer": ["under change history in the change log"]
    },
    "562": {
        "question": "for deals, which tool can be used to identify if the correct creative sizes are sent with the bid request?",
        "answer": ["deals troubleshooter"]
    },
    "563": {
        "question": "to activate the creative approvals process for a new creative, what step must be taken?",
        "answer": ["assign the creative to an active line item"]
    },
    "564": {
        "question": "when is a \u201cview\u201d counted for trueview campaigns?",
        "answer": ["each time the user clicks or watches 30 seconds or the entire video"]
    },
    "565": {
        "question": "when creating a new trueview campaign, how long should be allocated for creative review?",
        "answer": ["up to 24 hours"]
    },
    "566": {
        "question": "what report can help verify if pixels load correctly on a webpage?",
        "answer": ["floodlight"]
    },
    "567": {
        "question": "which two views show the revenue and conversion metrics for line items? (select two)",
        "answer": ["optimization view", "performance view"]
    },
    "568": {
        "question": "to send data from campaign manager to display & video 360, what initial step should be taken?",
        "answer": ["associate display &amp; video 360 in the advertiser's floodlight configuration in campaign manager"]
    },
    "569": {
        "question": "what is required for creative approval?",
        "answer": ["a valid landing page"]
    },
    "570": {
        "question": "which ad formats cannot be assigned to a single line item? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["trueview and video", "video and display"]
    },
    "571": {
        "question": "how can a profit margin be applied to the revenue metric?",
        "answer": ["assign a media cost markup to the partner revenue model"]
    },
    "572": {
        "question": "which exchanges have their own creative audit process?",
        "answer": ["appnexus, google ads manager, brightroll"]
    },
    "573": {
        "question": "what data cannot be evaluated with a standard or general performance report?",
        "answer": ["the match ratio of third- and first-party audience segments"]
    },
    "574": {
        "question": "what are two ways to make bulk changes within display & video 360 campaigns? select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["naviagate to insertion order &lt; line item level &lt; select line item &lt; action <bulk edit<=\"\" strong=\"\"></bulk>", "use structured data files (sdf)"]
    },
    "575": {
        "question": "what timezone is applied to inline charts and metrics data?",
        "answer": ["the advertiser's timezone"]
    },
    "576": {
        "question": "how can a campaign be activated after creating it?",
        "answer": ["select the activate dropdown for the campaign, line items, and insertion orders"]
    },
    "577": {
        "question": "to access a first-party audience list from a floodlight tag in display & video 360, what step should be taken in campaign manager?",
        "answer": ["assign the floodlight tag to an audience list "]
    },
    "578": {
        "question": "how can a group of urls be excluded across advertisers?",
        "answer": ["create a channel of urls and exclude it in advertiser or partner-level targeting"]
    },
    "579": {
        "question": "what are two ways to check why a private deal is not running? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["check the creative approval status", "use the deals troubleshooter"]
    },
    "580": {
        "question": "which two pacing scenarios represent spend-behavior that\u2019s working as intended? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["asap pacing line item spends the entire budget within the first couple of hours", "ahead pacing line item spends 120% of its expected daily spend"]
    },
    "581": {
        "question": "what should be used to investigate why a line item isn\u2019t winning the majority of qualifying open auction impressions?",
        "answer": ["the line item\u2018s impressions lost chart"]
    },
    "582": {
        "question": "which two insertion order and line item settings are required? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["pacing", "budget"]
    },
    "583": {
        "question": "what feature allows users to adjust fixed bids for different geographies or device types?",
        "answer": ["bid multipliers"]
    },
    "584": {
        "question": "what does an audit status of \u201cpending, servable\u201d mean?",
        "answer": ["the creative will serve, but may be rejected after policy review"]
    },
    "585": {
        "question": "how are line items affected when a user edits the default targeting for insertion orders?",
        "answer": ["existing line items are uneffected and new line items inherit the new default targeting"]
    },
    "586": {
        "question": "how can a site be blacklisted from an advertiser\u2019s media buys?",
        "answer": ["add the url to a channel that is assigned to the advertiser\u2018s exclusionary channel targeting"]
    },
    "587": {
        "question": "what step should an advertiser take to exclude sensitive categories using a supported third-party verification tool?",
        "answer": ["select the integrated third-party from \u201cother verification services\u201d in brand safety targeting"]
    },
    "588": {
        "question": "when creating new video line items, what are two execution methods that save time? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["duplicate video line items, then make bulk edits to targeting", "use structured data files to bulk upload new video line items"]
    },
    "589": {
        "question": "what is the correct display & video 360 account hierarchy?",
        "answer": ["partner &gt; advertiser &gt; campaign &gt; insertion order &gt; line item &gt; creative"]
    },
    "590": {
        "question": "how are creatives assigned to a line item?",
        "answer": ["select the creative to assign in the line item\u2018s creative section"]
    },
    "591": {
        "question": "what report can identify when a campaign overspent the budget?",
        "answer": ["basic or standard report, grouped by \u201ctime of day\u201d"]
    },
    "592": {
        "question": "how can a line item\u2019s potential reach be increased from 1k to 1m targeted impressions?",
        "answer": ["remove targeting such as keywords and exclusionary site lists"]
    },
    "593": {
        "question": "to duplicate a line item, what steps must be taken?",
        "answer": ["select the line item, click \u201caction,\u201d and then \u201cduplicate\u201d"]
    },
    "594": {
        "question": "to optimize the campaign towards viewability, which two approaches can an advertiser take? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["set the bid strategy to viewable cpm (vcpm)", "assign viewability targeting"]
    },
    "595": {
        "question": "what are two google audiences? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["affinity", "in market"]
    },
    "596": {
        "question": "which three settings could prevent deals from meeting their ad-serving goals? (select three)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["geotargeting and bid strategies", "demographics and audience targeting", "brand safety and sensitive category targeting"]
    },
    "597": {
        "question": "which two objectives can be selected as a campaign goal? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["drive offline or in-store sales", "raise awareness of my brand or product"]
    },
    "598": {
        "question": "what step would be taken to verify that conversion pixels are implemented and load correctly?",
        "answer": ["generate a pixel load report grouped by the conversion pixel(s)"]
    },
    "599": {
        "question": "which two options must be true to use open optimization? (select two)",
        "answer": ["more than one row in the feed must be eligible to serve", "in \u201cstep 3: manage rules\u201d rotation must be set to \u201coptimized\u201d"]
    },
    "600": {
        "question": "what tool makes it possible to preview a creative on a mobile device that\u2019s linked to a studio account?",
        "answer": ["creative preview app"]
    },
    "601": {
        "question": "echo remarketing uses dynamic content from what source?",
        "answer": ["custom floodlight variables"]
    },
    "602": {
        "question": "what dynamic strategy uses a naming convention to replace numeric campaign manager ids?",
        "answer": ["dynamic targeting keys"]
    },
    "603": {
        "question": "where are dynamic profiles located?",
        "answer": ["in the dynamic content tab next to advertiser name"]
    },
    "604": {
        "question": "the html5 enabler should be added to which tag in a creative\u2019s html file?",
        "answer": ["<head>", "<head>"]
    },
    "605": {
        "question": "in what section of studio can users upload and manage ad files?",
        "answer": ["creative"]
    },
    "606": {
        "question": "what type of creative appears within a set of borders and doesn\u2019t expand or cover a website\u2019s content?",
        "answer": ["banner creative"]
    },
    "607": {
        "question": "in what section of studio can users create and manage dynamic profiles?",
        "answer": ["dynamic content"]
    },
    "608": {
        "question": "what values are included in the targeting column of a remarketing feed?",
        "answer": ["floodlight audience list ids"]
    },
    "609": {
        "question": "which three elements are required for a dynamic creative? (select three)",
        "answer": ["studio creative", "dynamic content", "studio profile"]
    },
    "610": {
        "question": "what step must be taken before initiating a fullscreen expansion?",
        "answer": ["check that the enabler has been initialized"]
    },
    "611": {
        "question": "which two methods can be used to connect dynamic data to an element in the creative?(select two)",
        "answer": ["binding in google web designer", "custom javascript"]
    },
    "612": {
        "question": "which two methods can be used to build dynamic creatives for studio? (select two)",
        "answer": ["google web designer", "hand-coded html + javascript"]
    },
    "613": {
        "question": "what steps should be taken under manage data to upload a new feed to the studio profile?",
        "answer": ["select new content, then content source, and click \u201cstart import\u201d"]
    },
    "614": {
        "question": "what user access level allows read and write access to create or edit a dynamic profile and feed?",
        "answer": ["content owner"]
    },
    "615": {
        "question": "how many studio profiles can a dynamic creative be linked to?",
        "answer": ["1"]
    },
    "616": {
        "question": "what are two creative elements that can be dynamic? (select two)",
        "answer": ["clickthrough urls", "text"]
    },
    "617": {
        "question": "how can a studio profile be edited without impacting the live campaign?",
        "answer": ["create a new profile using the existing feed"]
    },
    "618": {
        "question": "what\u2019s the most efficient way to target one headline to 10 different audience ids in a feed?",
        "answer": ["add 10 comma-separated audience ids into one cell"]
    },
    "619": {
        "question": "in what product are dynamic targeting keys created?",
        "answer": ["campaign manager"]
    },
    "620": {
        "question": "which two variables can be used to optimize the rotation of dynamic creatives? (select two)",
        "answer": ["click-through rate (ctr)", "click-through-conversion rate"]
    },
    "621": {
        "question": "which three rotation settings are available in studio? (select three)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["weighted", "random", "optimized"]
    },
    "622": {
        "question": "in what section of studio are creative images and videos stored?",
        "answer": ["assets"]
    },
    "623": {
        "question": "what field type is used for data pass targeting in a dynamic profile?",
        "answer": ["custom value"]
    },
    "624": {
        "question": "what is the asset library file size limit per upload for video files?",
        "answer": ["60mb"]
    },
    "625": {
        "question": "when a feed contains a column of dynamic clickthrough urls, what function will a handcoded creative use?",
        "answer": ["enabler .exitoverride()"]
    },
    "626": {
        "question": "what action occurs when assets are uploaded to the creative section?",
        "answer": ["assets are copied to the asset library"]
    },
    "627": {
        "question": "when a user generates a dynamic preview and receives the error \u201ccan\u2019t show a preview because you haven\u2019t set a default creative or your applied filters don\u2019t match any feed rows,\u201d what first step should be taken to troubleshoot the error?",
        "answer": ["check if the correct feed filtering parameters were applied in the preview panel"]
    },
    "628": {
        "question": "which two targeting types are supported in studio for dynamic creatives? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["geo-targeting", "audience targeting"]
    },
    "629": {
        "question": "what is the method most often used to define the dynamic content for a creative?",
        "answer": ["spreadsheet"]
    },
    "630": {
        "question": "what configuration setting eliminates duplicate conversions between advertisers?",
        "answer": ["shared floodlight configuration"]
    },
    "631": {
        "question": "what is shown in the \u201clast sync\u201d details tab? (select two)",
        "answer": ["the time that the sync occurred", "the number of errors during the sync"]
    },
    "632": {
        "question": "which three features can be used to integrate offline conversion data?(select three)",
        "answer": ["sftp", "bulksheets", "search ads 360 api"]
    },
    "633": {
        "question": "when campaign manager isn\u2019t used as the ad server, what should search ads 360 advertisers link to in campaign manager?",
        "answer": ["advertiser"]
    },
    "634": {
        "question": "when setting a cpa, ers, or roas target for a bid strategy, how much conversion history should be considered?",
        "answer": ["3-4 weeks"]
    },
    "635": {
        "question": "at which three levels can bid strategies be applied? (select three)",
        "answer": ["keyword", "ad group", "campaign"]
    },
    "636": {
        "question": "what two floodlight activity group types can be set up? (select two)",
        "answer": ["counter", "sales"]
    },
    "637": {
        "question": "what metrics estimate conversions that measure user behavior across devices and environments?",
        "answer": ["cross-environment metrics"]
    },
    "638": {
        "question": "what function do valuetrack parameters perform?",
        "answer": ["dynamically insert information"]
    },
    "639": {
        "question": "which three features can a call-tracking partner use to send data to search ads 360? (select three)",
        "answer": ["campaign manager api", "bulksheets", "search ads 360 api"]
    },
    "640": {
        "question": "during the first week of an active bid strategy, which two changes can potentially impact the learning period? (select two)",
        "answer": ["decrease maximum bid in the bid strategy setting 40%", "decrease cpa target of bid strategy 60%"]
    },
    "641": {
        "question": "which three changes can a user set up using scheduled edits? (select three)",
        "answer": ["lower bids on keywords during weekends", "raise bids on keywords every monday at 7am", "activate ads or keywords at a specific time"]
    },
    "642": {
        "question": "what floodlight tag measures purchases and revenue on a website?",
        "answer": ["transaction"]
    },
    "643": {
        "question": "what are two key differentiators in functionality between labels and business data?",
        "answer": ["ability to pivot metrics within search ads 360", "ability to attach a business calendar"]
    },
    "644": {
        "question": "data exclusion events exclude data for a minimum of how many hours?",
        "answer": ["24 hours"]
    },
    "645": {
        "question": "which three frequencies can be scheduled for reports? (select three)",
        "answer": ["monthly", "daily", "weekly"]
    },
    "646": {
        "question": "which attribute may be used to upload paid search offline conversions via the campaign manager api?",
        "answer": ["gclid"]
    },
    "647": {
        "question": "what action should be used to pass a conversion attribute (such as shipping cost)?",
        "answer": ["set up custom floodlight variable as a metric"]
    },
    "648": {
        "question": "which two changes does an advertiser manager have permission to make to an advertiser account? (select two)",
        "answer": ["edit advertiser settings", "edit advertiser components"]
    },
    "649": {
        "question": "what could prevent inventory management from making changes to a campaign?",
        "answer": ["manual edits to campaign name or status"]
    },
    "650": {
        "question": "what type of bid strategy is supported by the forecasting tool?",
        "answer": ["conversions or revenue"]
    },
    "651": {
        "question": "what feature provides audience lists to display & video 360 or google ads based on search clicks recorded by search ads 360?",
        "answer": ["remarketing lists"]
    },
    "652": {
        "question": "what feature may be used to report on a specific floodlight conversion? \u2022 custom metric",
        "answer": ["custom column"]
    },
    "653": {
        "question": "what occurs when auto-tagging is enabled?",
        "answer": ["a google click id is appended to all landing page urls"]
    },
    "654": {
        "question": "what feature may be used to edit custom floodlight variable data?",
        "answer": ["search ads 360 api"]
    },
    "655": {
        "question": "which two conversion sources can be reported in custom columns? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["floodlight", "google ads conversion trackers"]
    },
    "656": {
        "question": "what attribution model assigns all credit to the last click on a paid search ad before a conversion?",
        "answer": ["last paid search interaction"]
    },
    "657": {
        "question": "which two constraints can an advertiser select on their conversion-based bid strategies? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["max cpa", "position"]
    },
    "658": {
        "question": "which two methods can be used to send an executive report to a user with no access to search ads 360? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["link to a shared version of the generated report", "send a downloaded pdf or excel file"]
    },
    "659": {
        "question": "which two column categories appear in formula columns? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["engine metrics", "conversion metrics"]
    },
    "660": {
        "question": "what feature is used to track unsupported ad types that specify their own landing page or google display network and gmail promoted campaigns?",
        "answer": ["placeholder keyword"]
    },
    "661": {
        "question": "if an engine account is set to a different currency than an advertiser, metrics will appear in what currency when scoped to the engine level?",
        "answer": ["engine\u2019s currency"]
    },
    "662": {
        "question": "what does it mean when the \u201cstop sync\u201d button is greyed out?",
        "answer": ["the sync is applying updates."]
    },
    "663": {
        "question": "bulksheets can be used to complete which two tasks? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["create labels", "upload offline conversions"]
    },
    "664": {
        "question": "how often is google ads, bing ads, and baidu data refreshed in search ads 360?",
        "answer": ["2 hours"]
    },
    "665": {
        "question": "what level should be used to evaluate performance of a bid strategy?",
        "answer": ["bid strategy"]
    },
    "666": {
        "question": "which level\u2019s settings cannot be edited with bulksheets? (select two)",
        "answer": ["advertiser", "network"]
    },
    "667": {
        "question": "when a reporting view is saved, who has access to the view?",
        "answer": ["all users within that advertiser"]
    },
    "668": {
        "question": "which three items can a bid strategy consider when optimizing the performance of a bidding portfolio as a whole? (select three)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["keywords / product groups", "ad groups", "campaigns"]
    },
    "669": {
        "question": "which three requirements must be met to run a successful ad copy test? (select three)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["each ad must contain only one landing page url", "minimum number of required impressions for each ad group", "ads must only include one ad copy test at a time"]
    },
    "670": {
        "question": "which two methods can be used to pass conversion attributes such as model type, color, and year of production through a floodlight activity? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["set up a custom floodlight variable in google tag manager", "set up a custom floodlight variable as a dimension in search ads 360"]
    },
    "671": {
        "question": "which three modifiers can be automated by a bid strategy? (select three)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["location target bid adjustments", "mobile bid adjustments", "remarketing target bid adjustments"]
    },
    "672": {
        "question": "at which two levels can url templates be set up? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["campaigns", "engine"]
    },
    "673": {
        "question": "which two types of uploads can be made through an sftp endpoint? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["bulksheets", "conversions"]
    },
    "674": {
        "question": "when a search ads 360 advertiser is linked to campaign manager, which product sets the timezone?",
        "answer": ["campaign manager"]
    },
    "675": {
        "question": "what step would be taken to check if an inventory management template has created any entities?",
        "answer": ["apply an \u201cinventory template id\u201d filter"]
    },
    "676": {
        "question": "if bids on keywords in a bid strategy are manually overwritten, how long will it take for the bid strategy to resume bidding on those keywords?",
        "answer": ["24 hours"]
    },
    "677": {
        "question": "which three urls are involved in a landing page test? (select three)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["experiment", "control", "original "]
    },
    "678": {
        "question": "in what order should new entities be created (assuming no campaigns already exist)?",
        "answer": ["campaign &gt; ad group &gt; ad &gt; keyword"]
    },
    "679": {
        "question": "what permissions are needed to create an advertiser?",
        "answer": ["agency manager"]
    },
    "680": {
        "question": "when a search ads 360 advertiser is added with a different currency than the linked campaign manager advertiser, which product sets the currency for that search ads 360 advertiser?",
        "answer": ["search ads 360"]
    },
    "681": {
        "question": "what setting should be applied to a floodlight tag passing offline conversion data?",
        "answer": ["primary source is offline"]
    },
    "682": {
        "question": "what is the search ads 360 account hierarchy?",
        "answer": ["agency &gt; advertiser &gt; engine &gt; campaign &gt; keyword &gt; ad group &gt; ad"]
    },
    "683": {
        "question": "what conversion data can be uploaded using bulksheets?",
        "answer": ["offline conversion data"]
    },
    "684": {
        "question": "at which three levels can automated rules be set up? (select three)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["engines", "campaigns", "keywords"]
    },
    "685": {
        "question": "which three engines are supported by the search ads 360 api? (select three)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["bing", "gemini", "google ads"]
    },
    "686": {
        "question": "where can a saved web query be found?",
        "answer": ["in the left-hand menu, click downloads then web query"]
    },
    "687": {
        "question": "if an engine account is set to a different timezone than an advertiser, in which timezone will floodlight metrics appear when scoped to the advertiser level?",
        "answer": ["the advertiser\u2019s timezone"]
    },
    "688": {
        "question": "which two types of campaigns do bid strategy opportunities analyze? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["bing ads manual campaigns", "google ads manual campaigns"]
    },
    "689": {
        "question": "which three landing page tests are available in search ads 360? (select three)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["desktop landing page test", "mobile landing page test", "all devices landing page test"]
    },
    "690": {
        "question": "what bid strategy goal should be used to create a custom strategy with multiple ers, roas, and cpa targets?",
        "answer": ["advanced targeting"]
    },
    "691": {
        "question": "which two filters are available in the change history report? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["campaign", "change type "]
    },
    "692": {
        "question": "which two conversion sources can be selected in bid strategies? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["floodlight", "google analytics"]
    },
    "693": {
        "question": "campaigns can only be copied within the same engine account for which two engines? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["bing ads", "yahoo gemini"]
    },
    "694": {
        "question": "what is the default attribution model for floodlight?",
        "answer": ["last click"]
    },
    "695": {
        "question": "which two segments cannot be applied to reporting data? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["user id", "attribution model"]
    },
    "696": {
        "question": "which two features may be used to upload offline conversion data to a search ads 360 keyword id? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["bulksheets", "search ads 360 api"]
    },
    "697": {
        "question": "which two user types can activate the conversion api? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["agency manager", "advertiser manager"]
    },
    "698": {
        "question": "which two types of goals can be targeted in bid strategies? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["conversion", "revenue"]
    },
    "699": {
        "question": "counters and total interactions metrics are available for which type of creatives?",
        "answer": ["creatives built in studio"]
    },
    "700": {
        "question": "what are two video verification metrics? (select two)",
        "answer": ["video prominence score", "audio muted at start"]
    },
    "701": {
        "question": "what ad setting ensures a qualified user will always be served a city-targeted ad first over a country-targeted ad when both ads are assigned to the same placement?",
        "answer": ["priority"]
    },
    "702": {
        "question": "what settings are required to give a user reporting access for a single advertiser?",
        "answer": ["create a user profile with a reporting-only user role, and filter for that advertiser"]
    },
    "703": {
        "question": "what are three benefits of using internal redirect tags? (select three)",
        "answer": ["reduce latency on ad-serving", "standardize a counting method with platform publishers", "richer domain information in verification"]
    },
    "704": {
        "question": "what ad setting limits the number of times that ad can be shown to a particular user?",
        "answer": ["frequency cap"]
    },
    "705": {
        "question": "which three workflows can be used to make bulk edits? (select three)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["the edit multiple button", "campaign spreadsheet upload", "the dcm/dfa reporting and trafficking api"]
    },
    "706": {
        "question": "what level is used to calculate conversions if the lookback window differs between objects?",
        "answer": ["placement level"]
    },
    "707": {
        "question": "at what level can landing pages be set, so they are the same across multiple ads?",
        "answer": ["creative"]
    },
    "708": {
        "question": "where would purchased inventory for a campaign be entered in campaign manager?",
        "answer": ["placements"]
    },
    "709": {
        "question": "when assets are added to an existing creative, where will these updates be reflected?",
        "answer": ["within the ads where the creatives are assigned"]
    },
    "710": {
        "question": "when using a placement media cost cap, what will happen once the cap is reached?",
        "answer": ["campaign manager will stop calculating and reporting media cost for the placement moving forward"]
    },
    "711": {
        "question": "what does an \u201cexecution channel\u201d represent in the planning process?",
        "answer": ["the \u201clink\u201d from the inventory in a media plan to a campaign manager campaign where placements can be executed"]
    },
    "712": {
        "question": "what must a floodlight tag include to capture product data alongside a conversion?",
        "answer": ["custom floodlight variable"]
    },
    "713": {
        "question": "which conditions must be true in order to designate an advertiser as a \u201cchild\u201d?select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["there aren\u2019t any floodlight activities associated with the \u201cchild\u201d advertiser", "the advertiser doesn\u2019t have any \u201cchild\u201d advertisers associated with it"]
    },
    "714": {
        "question": "which two methods count impressions on site-served creatives? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["tracking ads", "1\u00d71 impression tracker"]
    },
    "715": {
        "question": "where in campaign manager can the site id(s) required to push placements to display & video 360 be found?",
        "answer": ["next to its associated site name within a campaign"]
    },
    "716": {
        "question": "agency admin, agency trafficker, and site trafficker are examples of what?",
        "answer": ["user roles"]
    },
    "717": {
        "question": "in the insights tab in reporting, which two cards show a snapshot of performance? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["creative type", "device usage"]
    },
    "718": {
        "question": "if a publisher serves a placement tag after the campaign end date, what ad will serve?",
        "answer": ["the default ad"]
    },
    "719": {
        "question": "what section within a floodlight activity\u2019s settings allows users to add publisher tracking tags?",
        "answer": ["dynamic tags"]
    },
    "720": {
        "question": "what counting method tracks the number of sales made or items purchased?",
        "answer": ["sales activities"]
    },
    "721": {
        "question": "to link a display & video 360 advertiser, what initial step must be taken in campaign manager?",
        "answer": ["add the display &amp; video 360 partner id to the floodlight configuration as an association"]
    },
    "722": {
        "question": "for floodlight tags to properly attribute in-app conversions, what needs to happen within the app?",
        "answer": ["device id needs to be passed into the dc rdid parameter"]
    },
    "723": {
        "question": "when a \u201cplan\u201d is executed in planning, what information is pushed to campaign manager?",
        "answer": ["a list of placements you intend to purchase and the publishers you\u2019re buying inventory"]
    },
    "724": {
        "question": "which metric is not available in data transfer?",
        "answer": ["cross-environment conversions"]
    },
    "725": {
        "question": "what report tracks floodlight attribution in reporting?",
        "answer": ["path to conversion"]
    },
    "726": {
        "question": "what action can be taken to select which columns appear in the trafficking interface?",
        "answer": ["create a custom view"]
    },
    "727": {
        "question": "what html elements of a floodlight tag\u2019s iframe code identify the unique activity?",
        "answer": ["\u201ctype\u201d and \u201ccat\u201d"]
    },
    "728": {
        "question": "what is the limit to retrieve log data from a data transfer google bucket?",
        "answer": ["60 days"]
    },
    "729": {
        "question": "which functionalities are available to manage conversion data using the api? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["update", "insert"]
    },
    "730": {
        "question": "the insights tab in reporting shows the view performance against which three goals? (select three)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["cost per activity (cpa)", "click rate", "conversions per impression"]
    },
    "731": {
        "question": "what account structure should be used to share floodlight tags and audience lists between multiple advertisers?",
        "answer": ["a parent/child relationship"]
    },
    "732": {
        "question": "what timezone is used in data transfer (dt) timestamps for impression and click files?",
        "answer": ["coordinated universal time (utc)"]
    },
    "733": {
        "question": "which two tabs in reporting provide access to viewability data? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["report builder", "verification"]
    },
    "734": {
        "question": "what targeting rules display an ad to users who have viewed a product, but not purchased it?",
        "answer": ["positively target all product viewers and negatively target all product purchasers"]
    },
    "735": {
        "question": "what is the more cost-effective way to restrict ads served to a specific geographic region?",
        "answer": ["geo-targeting managed by a publisher or dsp"]
    },
    "736": {
        "question": "what feature can be used to combine log-level impression and click data for a custom reach analysis?",
        "answer": ["data transfer"]
    },
    "737": {
        "question": "unless default ads are disabled, what campaign trafficking action triggers the automatic creation of a default ad for display placements?",
        "answer": ["adding an image creative at the campaign level"]
    },
    "738": {
        "question": "what floodlight feature can be used to create a custom audience list that targets customers who purchased a specific product or service?",
        "answer": ["custom floodlight variable that captures the product or service id"]
    },
    "739": {
        "question": "what report shows how long it takes for a customer to convert after interacting with an ad?",
        "answer": ["time lag"]
    },
    "740": {
        "question": "when a top conversion paths report shows that most users enter the purchase cycle with a rich media interaction, what action can be taken to optimize the campaign?",
        "answer": ["create a sequential rotation with the rich media creative set first"]
    },
    "741": {
        "question": "when is an impression counted in reporting?",
        "answer": ["after a user\u2019s device indicates that the creative download has begun"]
    },
    "742": {
        "question": "what object in campaign manager is equivalent to a creative in display & video 360?",
        "answer": ["placement"]
    },
    "743": {
        "question": "if an agency trafficker can only see a subset of active campaigns within their account view, where would a agency admin go to adjust access to all campaigns?",
        "answer": ["user profile filters"]
    },
    "744": {
        "question": "which information can be extracted from the data in the verification tab? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["issues related to content", "errors for the ad tag related to implementation issues"]
    },
    "745": {
        "question": "what floodlight conversion counting method would report the first visit for each user within a given day?",
        "answer": ["unique"]
    },
    "746": {
        "question": "in a path to conversion report, when a user selects to \u201cpivot on interaction path,\u201d what are two major differences from the unpivoted report? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["each conversion gets its own row with interactions in separate columns", "rows and columns are flipped"]
    },
    "747": {
        "question": "paid search dimensions in report builder are compatible with what metric?",
        "answer": ["paid search revenue"]
    },
    "748": {
        "question": "at what level can landing pages be managed across campaigns?",
        "answer": ["advertiser"]
    },
    "749": {
        "question": "what happens when a user meets the frequency cap for an ad?",
        "answer": ["another ad or a default ad is served"]
    },
    "750": {
        "question": "audience lists created in campaign manager can be automatically shared with which linked applications? (select three)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["display &amp; video 360", "search ads 360"]
    },
    "751": {
        "question": "what report in report builder shows the number of unique users who have interacted with ads?",
        "answer": ["cookie reach overlap"]
    },
    "752": {
        "question": "when would a vpaid asset be used?",
        "answer": ["when vast is not supported"]
    },
    "753": {
        "question": "cross-environment conversion methodology takes into account what data sources? \u2022 data pools, cookies, audience ids",
        "answer": ["resettable device ids, cookies, anonymized google sign-ins"]
    },
    "754": {
        "question": "when the primary html5 assets get delayed, what will serve in a user\u2019s browser as it\u2019s loading?",
        "answer": ["polite load image"]
    },
    "755": {
        "question": "which two methods measure impressions served in a mobile app? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["serving mobile creative directly through campaign manager", "1\u00d71 impression tracker"]
    },
    "756": {
        "question": "what are two benefits of using the ins tag? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["eliminates the need for publishers to add cache-busters", "more robust verification data"]
    },
    "757": {
        "question": "when dynamic display creatives are published from studio, what creative type is set in campaign manager?",
        "answer": ["rich media"]
    },
    "758": {
        "question": "where are campaign manager and display & video 360 linked?",
        "answer": ["floodlight configuration"]
    },
    "759": {
        "question": "which two features may be used to log additional information about a click? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["event tags", "landing page url suffix"]
    },
    "760": {
        "question": "what action must occur for a team member to get access to data transfer files in google cloud storage?",
        "answer": ["add the team member\u2019s email to the google group associated with the cloud storage bucket"]
    },
    "761": {
        "question": "what is required to track mobile app conversions using floodlight tags?",
        "answer": ["a user-resettable device identifier passed to both floodlight tags and the ad tags running in apps"]
    },
    "762": {
        "question": "the \u201cdcm/dfa trafficking and reporting api\u201d can directly accomplish which two tasks? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["customize reporting", "upload conversions"]
    },
    "763": {
        "question": "what data is provided in video verification?",
        "answer": ["video player size and viewability"]
    },
    "764": {
        "question": "what attribution model uses floodlight data from both attributed and non-attributed conversions?",
        "answer": ["data-driven model"]
    },
    "765": {
        "question": "in which two tags can the keyword macro (%k) be added? (select two)select all correct responses",
        "answer": ["impression event", "tracking ad"]
    },
    "766": {
        "question": "what cost model only calculates cost for impressions measured as viewable by active view?",
        "answer": ["vcpm"]
    },

        "767": {
            "question": "you want to improve the relevance of an ad with a particular set of keywords. the goal is to increase the\u2026",
            "answer": ["adding more negative keywords."]
        },
        "768": {
            "question": "when creating an ad, how does greg know what it will look like to his potential customers?",
            "answer": ["as he types in his url, headline, and description, a preview of the mobile and desktop versions of his ad will appear."]
        },
        "769": {
            "question": "asam is learning about google ads search. he wants to know why a marketer might use callout extensions. for which activity are callout extensions beneficial?",
            "answer": ["highlight key information and unique selling points of a business"]
        },
        "770": {
            "question": "google ads was designed to help businesses achieve online success. to accomplish this, google ads was built\u2026",
            "answer": ["relevance, control, and results"]
        },
        "771": {
            "question": "your client, vince\u2019s veggies, wants to increase downloads of their popular recipe printouts. you suggest they create ad groups based on the cooking categories that appear on their website. what will they need to create in their first google search ad group? (choose two.)",
            "answer": ["keyword list", "default bid amount"]
        },
        "772": {
            "question": "what\u2019s the maximum number of ad extensions that can show for a particular query or device at any given time?",
            "answer": ["4"]
        },
        "773": {
            "question": "what is a main benefit of using search audience solutions?",
            "answer": ["they can help send the right message to the right customer with the right bid."]
        },
        "774": {
            "question": "a water-sports company specializes in custom-made watercrafts and accessories. their marketing manager\u2026",
            "answer": ["a green boat paddle", "travel on a paddle ship"]
        },
        "775": {
            "question": "what does performance planner automatically do?",
            "answer": ["forecasts how your current campaigns will perform in the future"]
        },
        "776": {
            "question": "clara is an advertising director who has been tasked with optimizing her company\u2019s google search campaign\u2026",
            "answer": ["to find how close her campaign is from potential ideal results"]
        },
        "777": {
            "question": "siona needs to make sure her ads are getting a minimum number of impressions on the top of the page\u2026",
            "answer": ["target impression share"]
        },
        "778": {
            "question": "which statement is true about serving relevant ad extensions?",
            "answer": ["they encourage users to make more informed decisions and take action."]
        },
        "779": {
            "question": "jimmy sells televisions on his website. he notices he\u2019s getting traffic from searches for a brand he\u2026",
            "answer": ["his ads won\u2019t be shown to users searching for the uncarried brand."]
        },
        "780": {
            "question": "what is the minimum number of users a remarketing list must have before being used with a remarketing\u2026",
            "answer": ["1,000 users"]
        },
        "781": {
            "question": "you\u2019re working on a google search ad that\u2019s not performing as expected. you specifically want more users to\u2026",
            "answer": ["changing the call-to-action message of the ad."]
        },
        "782": {
            "question": "match these search audience solutions with the benefits they can bring to",
            "answer": ["remarketing lists for search ads ", "detailed demographics", "in-market audiences ", "customer match"]
        },
        "783": {
            "question": "your google search text ad has three main components. the first is a headline, and the second is a description",
            "answer": ["the url displaying your website address."]
        },
        "784": {
            "question": "reggie manages the online marketing campaigns for a vitamin and supplement store. he launched a\u2026",
            "answer": ["getting more customers to learn about his products."]
        },
        "785": {
            "question": "you\u2019d like to improve an ad\u2019s perceived quality during an ad auction. what aspect of the ad will be most\u2026",
            "answer": ["improving the navigability of the landing page."]
        },
        "786": {
            "question": "brian manages his company\u2019s google search ads campaign. he regularly reviews the optimization score to make\u2026",
            "answer": ["key aspects of his accounts, including statistics, settings, and industry trends"]
        },
        "787": {
            "question": "silly sayings is seeing a lot of website traffic, but the company wants to generate more qualified leads\u2026",
            "answer": ["by providing users with relevant information up-front."]
        },
        "788": {
            "question": "what search network text ad component provides up to three fields of 30 characters each?",
            "answer": ["the headline component"]
        },
        "789": {
            "question": "rashid wants to raise awareness of his brand and build campaigns focused on branded terms. he doesn\u2019t have\u2026",
            "answer": ["target impression share"]
        },
        "790": {
            "question": "carrie owns a gardening store and uses a website to promote all the products she sells. a user saw a google\u2026",
            "answer": ["searching for related gardening information."]
        },
        "791": {
            "question": "john\u2019s company makes a great product and customers are happy with their purchases. unfortunately, few\u2026",
            "answer": ["with multiple headline and description options, responsive ads can compete in more auctions for a wider range of search terms.", "with lower costs-per-click, advertisers using responsive ads can afford to be in more daily auctions."]
        },
        "792": {
            "question": "you\u2019ve been tasked with marketing a new line of plumbing services, but you have a set budget you can\u2019t exceed.",
            "answer": ["google ads gives you control over your budget."]
        },
        "793": {
            "question": "karen has evaluated her google search ads campaign\u2019s optimization score after noticing that the campaign\u2019s\u2026",
            "answer": ["it will improve upon acceptance."]
        },
        "794": {
            "question": "swee yin\u2019s fashion-apparel department store runs a popular biannual sale on men\u2019s hats, with large discounts and surprise bonus items. she wants to tailor her google search campaign to highlight this sale. how can google search campaigns be tailored to promote her company\u2019s sales event?",
            "answer": ["by creating a new ad group for the sale.", "by setting campaign start/end dates."]
        },
        "795": {
            "question": "a golf enthusiast regularly watches instructional videos about golf, has recently searched for the best golf\u2026",
            "answer": ["affinity audience"]
        },
        "796": {
            "question": "samira recently opened an online potted plant store and needs to promote it. she chose google ads because\u2026",
            "answer": ["shopping campaigns, which promote her products by giving consumers detailed informationabout what she\u2019s selling before they click her ad."]
        },
        "797": {
            "question": "when visibility is the campaign goal, which bidding strategy should an advertiser choose?",
            "answer": ["target impression share"]
        },
        "798": {
            "question": "yan wants to attract customers specifically searching on google for time-b-gone, his company\u2019s unique office\u2026",
            "answer": ["landing pages from standard ad groups"]
        },
        "799": {
            "question": "you are working to improve the quality score of a google search ad by increasing your ectr. your goal is to\u2026",
            "answer": ["adding more specifics to the ad."]
        },
        "800": {
            "question": "helen\u2019s heating and air (hha) wants to encourage interest in their new smart refrigerators. they know that\u2026",
            "answer": ["smart refrigerator reviews", "energy-efficient fridge"]
        },
        "801": {
            "question": "john\u2019s plumbing prides itself on excellent customer service, especially during after-hours service calls\u2026",
            "answer": ["ad scheduling"]
        },
        "802": {
            "question": "francis wants to increase his google ads skills and optimize results for his clients. what two best practices\u2026",
            "answer": ["include three to five ads, and at least three extensions in each ad group.", "optimize the campaign\u2019s ad rotation for clicks or conversion actions."]
        },
        "803": {
            "question": "maria has been told that she should use the performance planner on a monthly basis. why should she do so?",
            "answer": ["to react to ever-changing external factors"]
        },
        "804": {
            "question": "what are two ways that performance planner can help reveal the possibilities across all your google ads\u2026",
            "answer": ["validation", "simulation"]
        },
        "805": {
            "question": "match each ad extension with the benefit it brings to a user\u2019s ad experience.",
            "answer": []
        },
        "806": {
            "question": "it is 10 a.m. and you are sitting in a train station in london, looking through your calendar on your tablet.",
            "answer": ["time", "interest", "intent", "device", "location"]
        },
        "807": {
            "question": "priya only has $500 a month to spend on her campaign, but she needs to drive as many potential customers as\u2026",
            "answer": ["maximize clicks"]
        },
        "808": {
            "question": "your company provides home-maintenance services, and you want to reach more potential customers\u2026",
            "answer": ["you can set your own budget and can change it at any time."]
        },
        "809": {
            "question": "carlton runs an adventure excursion company in south america. he\u2019d like to increase the number of people\u2026",
            "answer": ["researching south american holiday destinations online."]
        },
        "810": {
            "question": "google ads was constructed around three core principles, focused on helping businesses reach their online\u2026",
            "answer": ["control and results"]
        },
        "811": {
            "question": "you\u2019ve seen great results from your google search campaigns when using remarketing lists for search ads\u2026",
            "answer": ["use similar audiences to find new visitors for your site"]
        },
        "812": {
            "question": "bernadette\u2019s in charge of marketing a new product in a highly competitive segment. she\u2019s planning to launch\u2026",
            "answer": ["her business will have a competitive presence with similar businesses during searches."]
        },
        "813": {
            "question": "mario is working on a text ad that will run on the google search network. he filled in each component with\u2026",
            "answer": ["the description component"]
        },
        "814": {
            "question": "rebecca is a marketing executive at an airline company. she has been asked to plan her company\u2019s online\u2026",
            "answer": ["performance planner forecasting is powered by billions of google searches conducted eachweek.", "performance planner leverages machine learning for forecasting."]
        },
        "815": {
            "question": "what two ad extension types can also be served as automated ad extensions? (choose two.)",
            "answer": ["sitelink extension", "callout extension"]
        },
        "816": {
            "question": "an advertising executive takes over a google search ads campaign. on his google ads recommendations page he\u2026",
            "answer": ["<a>the campaign could be improved by 60% if the listed recommendations are followed</a>."]
        },
        "817": {
            "question": "what\u2019s the primary benefit of using structured snippet extensions in your ads?",
            "answer": ["gives users specific information about what you\u2019re offering, before they visit your website."]
        },
        "818": {
            "question": "automated bidding does the heavy lifting for advertisers on google ads. what does automated bidding use to\u2026",
            "answer": ["machine learning"]
        },
        "819": {
            "question": "trevor owns a manufacturing business that makes specialized hiking and rock-climbing gear. he\u2019s a small\u2026",
            "answer": ["display"]
        },
        "820": {
            "question": "bob\u2019s electronics company is launching a new television called ultraview1000. bob decides to use broad\u2026",
            "answer": ["bob\u2019s ad will appear if search terms contain some variation of his keyword, such as \u201ctv.\u201d"]
        },
        "821": {
            "question": "yan is working on a remarketing list for search ads campaign. which user could be added to a valid remarket\u2026",
            "answer": ["someone who has added items to a shopping basket on his company\u2019s website but thenabandoned it"]
        },
        "822": {
            "question": "as an advertiser, creating your first text ad in google ads is a simple five\u2026",
            "answer": ["first step:", "second step:", "third step:", "fourth step:", "fifth step: "]
        },
        "823": {
            "question": "what\u2019s a key objective in delivering ad extensions?",
            "answer": ["providing the right users with the right information at the right moment."]
        },
        "824": {
            "question": "ad extensions assist in providing users with which two things they want from their search experience?",
            "answer": ["relevant information", "information based on their moment"]
        },
        "825": {
            "question": "ginger\u2019s working on creating her first google search ad. she wants to create an inviting and relevant ad,\u2026",
            "answer": ["has a relevant headline", "includes a current promotion"]
        },
        "826": {
            "question": "lisa sells kitchen furniture through her website. while her sales are stable, she\u2019s concerned that they\u2019re\u2026",
            "answer": ["her business will have a competitive presence with similar businesses during searches."]
        },
        "827": {
            "question": "jerry\u2019s managing a google search campaign and would like to improve the position in which his ads appear\u2026",
            "answer": ["create a helpful, relevant landing page for the ad."]
        },
        "828": {
            "question": "what are two main benefits of using search audience solutions? (choose two.)",
            "answer": ["making the right bids when certain groups of people are searching for your product or services", "reaching different audience segments with unique messaging that is highly relevant to them"]
        },
        "829": {
            "question": "how is using non-last-click attribution conversions useful for performance planner forecasts?",
            "answer": ["to allocate budgets that drive incremental conversions"]
        },
        "830": {
            "question": "what can the performance planner assist you with?",
            "answer": ["to improve return on investment so you can drive more conversions within your target cpa(cost-per-acquisition)"]
        },
        "831": {
            "question": "what does layering an affinity audience with a broad keyword targeting campaign help you do?",
            "answer": ["ensure your ads are only seen by people who have demonstrated a qualified interestin your service and/or product(s)"]
        },
        "832": {
            "question": "what is one way that performance planner helps businesses increase sales?",
            "answer": ["by maximizing the number of conversions for a spend scenario"]
        },
        "833": {
            "question": "steven is an advertising executive at a large auto parts company. he uses his google ads recommendations\u2026",
            "answer": ["apply recommendations across multiple layers of his advertising strategy"]
        },
        "834": {
            "question": "singh\u2019s marketing company has created an enticing ad that receives many clicks. what effect will the ad\u2026",
            "answer": ["the higher expected click-through rate will lead to a higher ad rank."]
        },
        "835": {
            "question": "mary wants to run a text ad on the google search network. she\u2019s new to text ads and needs to start with the\u2026",
            "answer": ["headline, url, description"]
        },
        "836": {
            "question": "how can performance planner serve your business?",
            "answer": ["by optimizing your ad budget for maximum growth"]
        },
        "837": {
            "question": "wendy is setting up a customer match strategy to reach a list of prospective customers. what must she provide?",
            "answer": ["customer relationship management data"]
        },
        "838": {
            "question": "jim has created a google search ad with a bid of $5. two other advertisers in an auction have bids of $2.50\u2026",
            "answer": ["$2.51"]
        },
        "839": {
            "question": "trina is using automated bidding as part of her google ads search bidding strategy. why might she prefer\u2026",
            "answer": ["machine learning helps her set the appropriate bid for each and every auction."]
        },
        "840": {
            "question": "why is using the performance targets feature after utilizing the performance planner recommended?",
            "answer": ["this practice allows you to monitor targets set in the performance planner and to receive alerts and recommendations when a campaign is not on track."]
        },
        "841": {
            "question": "what are two ways dynamic search ads brings value to an advertising campaign?",
            "answer": ["it creates new ads automatically.", "it finds traffic an advertiser might miss."]
        },
        "842": {
            "question": "your google search ads optimization score is calculated by an algorithm that looks across key aspects of\u2026",
            "answer": ["industry data", "account settings"]
        },
        "843": {
            "question": "google ads reviews saved text ads to ensure they meet advertising policies before being shown to users\u2026",
            "answer": ["content and formatting."]
        },
        "844": {
            "question": "what\u2019s an example of an effective callout extension?",
            "answer": ["free returns"]
        },
        "845": {
            "question": "while managing a successful google ads campaign, why would you choose automated bidding instead of manual\u2026",
            "answer": ["because given the dynamic nature of google\u2019s auctions, the appropriate bid can often be a moving target that is challenging to reach at scale when using manual bidding"]
        },
        "846": {
            "question": "what does adding callout extensions to your google search ads enable you to do?",
            "answer": ["highlight information about value-adding attributes of your business, products, orservices."]
        },
        "847": {
            "question": "bob\u2019s electronics company has quite a buzz around a new television they\u2019re launching, called ultraview1000\u2026",
            "answer": ["bob\u2019s ad will appear if search terms contain at least all three of the keywords orvariations of those terms."]
        },
        "848": {
            "question": "you want to increase the relevance of a google search ad so it\u2019s more meaningful to potential customers\u2026",
            "answer": ["selecting distinct geographic areas.", "selecting only relevant languages in campaign setup."]
        },
        "849": {
            "question": "what content could be used for a structured snippet extension?",
            "answer": ["berlin, london, paris, singapore"]
        },
        "850": {
            "question": "hank wants to use a \u201cmaximize conversions\u201d campaign with the performance planner. which recommendation\u2026",
            "answer": ["a recommended average daily budget"]
        },
        "851": {
            "question": "which is required for an ad to be served to a user?",
            "answer": ["the keywords must be relevant to the search term."]
        },
        "852": {
            "question": "samira has been tasked with increasing the relevance of her company\u2019s ads. she has been told that she can\u2026",
            "answer": ["up to 15 headlines"]
        },
        "853": {
            "question": "using the performance planner on a monthly basis allows you to optimize which two aspects of an account?",
            "answer": ["bids", "budgets"]
        },
        "854": {
            "question": "alex has started a google search campaign designed to promote his online motorcycle accessories store\u2026",
            "answer": ["by showing his ad to people searching for related information about helmets."]
        },
        "855": {
            "question": "what can the performance planner recommend?",
            "answer": ["campaign-level target cpa (cost-per-acquisition)"]
        },
        "856": {
            "question": "what\u2019s an accurate description of callout extensions?",
            "answer": ["short, specific snippets of text that highlight value-adding attributes."]
        },
        "857": {
            "question": "trina sells dolls and accessories, and doesn\u2019t have much time to update her search campaigns with her ever\u2026",
            "answer": ["keyword lists can be automatically created based on website offerings."]
        },
        "858": {
            "question": "sarah\u2019s autos sells multiple automobile brands, showcasing used, pre-owned, and new vehicles. the company\u2019s\u2026",
            "answer": ["car", "automobile"]
        },
        "859": {
            "question": "which dynamic search ads option allows an advertiser to group web pages under custom labels?",
            "answer": ["page feeds"]
        },
        "860": {
            "question": "francine is advertising her company\u2019s newest video-editing software and related products. she knows that\u2026",
            "answer": ["more ads in an ad group means more options for success in an auction."]
        },
        "861": {
            "question": "in-market audiences would be suited to reach which user?",
            "answer": ["someone looking to purchase a new car"]
        },
        "862": {
            "question": "what ad extension is only available as a full automated ad extension?",
            "answer": ["seller ratings extension"]
        },
        "863": {
            "question": "how does automating your bid contribute to a successful google ads campaign?",
            "answer": ["automated bidding uses machine learning to algorithmically help you set the appropriatebid for each and every auction."]
        },
        "864": {
            "question": "google ads was designed to deliver three things to every advertiser: relevance, control, and results\u2026",
            "answer": ["by giving advertisers control over the maximum they spend per month."]
        },
        "865": {
            "question": "after running a google search ads campaign for several months, meredith notices sales of her advertised\u2026",
            "answer": ["the campaign could be improved by 78% if the listed recommendations are followed."]
        },
        "866": {
            "question": "marta\u2019s online store sells accessories for a widely used smartphone, and her current customer base shares a\u2026",
            "answer": ["location", "device type"]
        },
        "867": {
            "question": "tara is using search audiences to reach her most valuable customers. which direct benefit might she obtain by using search audience?",
            "answer": ["delivering a customized message to the right user at the correct bid"]
        },
        "868": {
            "question": "when should you use remarketing lists for search ads?",
            "answer": ["to reach people who have already engaged with your website in the past"]
        },
        "869": {
            "question": "marisol manages the online advertising campaigns for a chain of toy stores with both a physical and an online\u2026",
            "answer": ["shopping"]
        },
        "870": {
            "question": "when running remarketing lists for search ads campaigns, some audience lists have higher potential to convert",
            "answer": ["reached the checkout page but did not complete the purchase.", "added an item to the shopping basket but then abandoned it.", "visited the website in the past 7 days but did not convert.", "visited the website in the past 28 days but did not convert"]
        },
        "871": {
            "question": "leo is in charge of advertising for the clothing lines of a large manufacturer. he uses his google ads\u2026",
            "answer": ["the recommendations are tailored to the specific account."]
        },
        "872": {
            "question": "peggy owns a house-cleaning service. she built a booking website and is ready to promote her services online\u2026",
            "answer": ["search"]
        },
        "873": {
            "question": "karen\u2019s washing machine broke, so she\u2019s conducting a search on google to find a new one. she sees a number\u2026",
            "answer": ["ad relevance", "advertiser bid"]
        },
        "874": {
            "question": "why should campaigns with different marketing objectives be separated into different performance planner plans",
            "answer": ["so that spend is not reallocated between two different marketing objectives"]
        },
        "875": {
            "question": "google ads offers a variety of campaign types that determine where your ad will appear and the format in\u2026",
            "answer": ["search, display, video, shopping, and app"]
        },
        "876": {
            "question": "ideally, what\u2019s the minimum number of values you should aim for per header when using structured snippet\u2026",
            "answer": ["4"]
        },
        "877": {
            "question": "brenda\u2019s working on improving a google search ad\u2019s quality score so it potentially gets a better ad rank and\u2026",
            "answer": ["adding seasonal messaging during the holiday season."]
        },
        "878": {
            "question": "what is one of the reasons why an advertiser should consider using performance planner on a monthly basis?",
            "answer": ["auctions fluctuate all the time"]
        },
        "879": {
            "question": "ben is currently managing a campaign that has a total investment of $7,000, generates 1,400 conversions\u2026",
            "answer": ["an investment of $9,600 to generate 1,600 conversions with a cpa of $6"]
        },
        "880": {
            "question": "what is a valid recommendation that the performance planner can provide?",
            "answer": ["set a specific target cpa (cost-per-acquisition)"]
        },
        "881": {
            "question": "pete is the marketing director for an electric car company. he recently chose \u201cleads\u201d as his google search\u2026",
            "answer": ["increase e-mail list sign-ups from potential customers."]
        },
        "882": {
            "question": "gina wants to be able to try out multiple combinations of headlines and descriptions in order to optimize her",
            "answer": ["greater flexibility", "more relevance"]
        },
        "883": {
            "question": "bob\u2019s electronics company is launching the sale of a new television, ultraview1000. bob decides to use phrase match in his search ads campaign because he wants searches that contain ultraview1000 to show his ad. how else will phrase match benefit bob\u2019s campaign",
            "answer": ["bob\u2019s ad will show on searches for ultraview1000 and additional words before and after."]
        },
        "884": {
            "question": "theo is looking to improve his google search ads campaign. on his google ads recommendations page, he notices",
            "answer": ["the campaign could improve up to 25% by following the listed recommendations."]
        },
        "885": {
            "question": "why does automating your bid vs. using manual bidding contribute to a successful google ads campaign?",
            "answer": ["if you don\u2019t bid efficiently, you could miss valuable conversions."]
        },
        "886": {
            "question": "when creating a text ad for the search network, advertisers will need to include three distinct components.",
            "answer": ["the description"]
        },
        "887": {
            "question": "you can leverage google ads\u2019 automated bidding strategy to help get the most from your advertising budget.",
            "answer": []
        },
        "888": {
            "question": "jasmine is the director of marketing for a chain of clothing stores. she\u2019s been given a set budget and needs",
            "answer": ["maximize clicks"]
        },
        "889": {
            "question": "when are automated extensions, such as seller ratings, shown?",
            "answer": ["when google predicts they\u2019ll improve ad performance."]
        },
        "890": {
            "question": "tomacz wants to use a google search ads campaign to capture the attention of customers searching for camping",
            "answer": ["displayed ads are relevant to a potential customer\u2019s google search."]
        },
        "891": {
            "question": "sandy, an expert on search marketing, knows she should use extensions effectively in order to optimize her",
            "answer": ["use at least three extensions in each campaign or ad group."]
        },
        "892": {
            "question": "with dynamic search ads, what does the advertiser provide?",
            "answer": ["a list of web pages"]
        },
        "893": {
            "question": "as a digital strategist, jared wants to add something extra to his ads to give users more incentive to click..",
            "answer": ["up to 15 characters in each"]
        },
        "894": {
            "question": "why should your business use performance planner?",
            "answer": ["it makes recommendations that are validated using machine learning."]
        },
        "895": {
            "question": "how can ad extensions contribute to increasing user engagement?",
            "answer": ["by addressing a user\u2019s intent, device, and location."]
        },
        "896": {
            "question": "organize these steps in the correct order to set up an effective customer match strategy\u2026",
            "answer": ["segment a customer list, based on a desired marketing action.", "upload the list to google ads.", "translate the list into an audience list and make it available for targeting.", "customize your creatives with special offers or incentives that are specific to this audience."]
        },
        "897": {
            "question": "you manage marketing for a small business on a tight budget, yet you need to reach as many people as possible.",
            "answer": ["with google ads, you can choose a maximum amount to spend per month."]
        },
        "898": {
            "question": "which search audience solution would assist you in finding new customers that share the behaviors and\u2026",
            "answer": ["similar audiences for search"]
        },
        "899": {
            "question": "laverne created her first google search campaign for her yoga school. she selects the google search network\u2026",
            "answer": ["extends her reach to additional sites."]
        },
        "900": {
            "question": "rina notices that her ad\u2019s average cost per click (cpc) is significantly higher than the industry benchmark\u2026",
            "answer": ["improve the ad\u2019s quality score."]
        },
        "901": {
            "question": "mary is tasked with designing an advertising campaign for her company, an online pet food store and app\u2026",
            "answer": ["search, display, video, shopping, and app"]
        },
        "902": {
            "question": "which user data can be uploaded when creating a customer match strategy? (choose two.)\u2026",
            "answer": ["e-mail address", "mailing address"]
        },
        "903": {
            "question": "marta has a tight marketing budget and needs to use a strategy that can drive customers to her website\u2026",
            "answer": ["maximize clicks"]
        },
        "904": {
            "question": "each similar audience has its seed list members removed to ensure what?",
            "answer": ["that no user overlaps between a similar list and its seed list"]
        },
        "905": {
            "question": "jamie wants to focus on selling her overstocked blue saucepans. she sets up keywords using a broad-match\u2026",
            "answer": ["she doesn\u2019t have to think of all the related saucepan keywords.", "she can easily select the color she wants to focus on."]
        }
    }





JaroWrinker  = function (s1, s2) {
    var m = 0;

    if ( s1.length === 0 || s2.length === 0 ) {
        return 0;
    };

    if ( s1 === s2 ) {
        return 1;
    };

    var range     = (Math.floor(Math.max(s1.length, s2.length) / 2)) - 1,
        s1Matches = new Array(s1.length),
        s2Matches = new Array(s2.length);

    for ( i = 0; i < s1.length; i++ ) {
        var low  = (i >= range) ? i - range : 0,
            high = (i + range <= s2.length) ? (i + range) : (s2.length - 1);

        for ( j = low; j <= high; j++ ) {
        if ( s1Matches[i] !== true && s2Matches[j] !== true && s1[i] === s2[j] ) {
            ++m;
            s1Matches[i] = s2Matches[j] = true;
            break;
        };
        };
    };

    if ( m === 0 ) {
        return 0;
    };

    var k = n_trans = 0;

    for ( i = 0; i < s1.length; i++ ) {
        if ( s1Matches[i] === true ) {
        for ( j = k; j < s2.length; j++ ) {
            if ( s2Matches[j] === true ) {
            k = j + 1;
            break;
            };
        };

        if ( s1[i] !== s2[j] ) {
            ++n_trans;
        };
        };
    };

    var weight = (m / s1.length + m / s2.length + (m - (n_trans / 2)) / m) / 3,
        l      = 0,
        p      = 0.1;

    if ( weight > 0.7 ) {
        while ( s1[l] === s2[l] && l < 4 ) {
        ++l;
        };

        weight = weight + l * p * (1 - weight);
    };

    return weight;
};


var answerFound = false;
var questionTodo;
var possibleAnswers = [];
var answerCount = document.querySelectorAll("#assessment_response_form > div.question__answer > ul > li").length;

if (document.querySelector('.checkbox__label')){

    questionTodo    = document.querySelector("div.question__question > p").innerText.trim().toLowerCase();
    possibleAnswers = document.querySelectorAll("#assessment_response_form > div.question__answer > ul > li");

    var rightAnswers = matchQuestions(questionTodo,possibleAnswers);
    document.querySelector('div.question__question > p').innerHTML = "<div style='border:1px solid black'><h3>I am "+(Math.floor(rightAnswers.score * 100))+"% sure.</h3><p>This is the question we matched:</p><p>"+rightAnswers.question+"</p><br><p>The originals question:<br>"+questionTodo+"</p><br><p>The following answers should be correct: <br><strong>"+rightAnswers.answer+"</strong></p></div>";


    for (var x = 0; x < answerCount; x++){
        var answerChoice = document.querySelector("#assessment_response_form > div.question__answer > ul > li:nth-child("+(x+1)+") > label > span.checkbox__label");
        if(answerChoice){
            for(var i = 0; i < rightAnswers.answer.length; i++){
                if(rightAnswers.answer[i] === answerChoice.innerText.toLowerCase().trim()){
                    answerFound = true;
                    document.querySelector("#choice_id_"+x).click();
                };
            };
        };
    };

    if (!answerFound){
        var listFun = [];
        var oldScore = 0;
        var newScore = 0;
        var oldAnswer;
        var newAnswer;
        var likelyAnswer = {
            ourAnswer: "fuck you",
            theirAnswer: "fuck me",
            score: 0
        };

        for (var x = 0; x < answerCount; x++){
            var answerChoice = document.querySelector("#assessment_response_form > div.question__answer > ul > li:nth-child("+(x+1)+") > label > span.checkbox__label");
            if(answerChoice){
                for(var y = 0; y < rightAnswers.answer.length; y++){
                    var answ = answerChoice.innerText.toLowerCase();
                    oldAnswer = rightAnswers.answer[y];

                    oldScore = JaroWrinker(rightAnswers.answer[y], answ);
                    if(oldScore > newScore) {
                        newScore = oldScore;
                        newAnswer = oldAnswer;

                        likelyAnswer = {
                            ourAnswer: newAnswer,
                            theirAnswer: answ,
                            score: newScore
                        };
                        listFun.push(likelyAnswer);
                    };
                var sorted = listFun.sort(function(a,b,){
                    return b.score - a.score;
                });
                };
            };
        };


    var newSorted = sorted.slice(0, rightAnswers.answer.length);
    var strOur = '<ul>';
    newSorted.forEach(function(el) {
        strOur += '<li>'+ el.ourAnswer + '</li>';
    }); 
    strOur += '</ul>';

    var strTheir = '<ul>';
    newSorted.forEach(function(el) {
        strTheir += '<li>'+ el.theirAnswer + '</li>';
    }); 
    strTheir += '</ul>';

    document.querySelector('div.question__question > p').innerHTML = "<div style='border:1px solid black'><h3>I am "+(Math.floor(likelyAnswer.score * 100))+"% sure.</h3><p>Their answer choice:</p><p>"+strTheir+"</p><p>Our answer: <strong>"+strOur+"</strong></p></div>";
    
    };

} else {

    questionTodo    = document.querySelector("div.question__question > p").innerText.trim().toLowerCase();
    possibleAnswers = document.querySelectorAll("#assessment_response_form > div.question__answer > ul > li");

    var rightAnswers = matchQuestions(questionTodo,possibleAnswers);

    document.querySelector('div.question__question > p').innerHTML = "<div style='border:1px solid black'><h3>I am "+(Math.floor(rightAnswers.score * 100))+"% sure.</h3><p>This is the question we matched:</p><p>"+rightAnswers.question+"</p><br><p>The originals question:<br>"+questionTodo+"</p><br><p>The following answers should be correct: <br><strong>"+rightAnswers.answer+"</strong></p></div>";

    for (var x = 0; x < answerCount; x++){
        var answerChoice = document.querySelector("#assessment_response_form > div.question__answer > ul > li:nth-child("+(x+1)+") > label > span.radio__label");
        if(answerChoice){
            for(var i = 0; i < rightAnswers.answer.length; i++){
                if(rightAnswers.answer[i] === answerChoice.innerText.toLowerCase()){
                    answerFound = true;
                    document.querySelector("#choice_id_"+x).click();
                };
            };
        };
    };

    if (!answerFound){
        var oldScore = 0;
        var newScore = 0;
        var oldAnswer;
        var newAnswer;
        var likelyAnswer = {
            ourAnswer: "fuck you",
            theirAnswer: "fuck me",
            score: 0
        };

        for (var x = 0; x < answerCount; x++){
            var answerChoice = document.querySelector("#assessment_response_form > div.question__answer > ul > li:nth-child("+(x+1)+") > label > span.radio__label");
            if(answerChoice){
                for(var i = 0; i < rightAnswers.answer.length; i++){
                    var answ = answerChoice.innerText.toLowerCase();
                    oldAnswer = rightAnswers.answer[i];

                    oldScore = JaroWrinker(rightAnswers.answer[i], answ);

                    if(oldScore > newScore) {
                        newScore = oldScore;
                        newAnswer = oldAnswer;

                        likelyAnswer = {
                            ourAnswer: newAnswer,
                            theirAnswer: answ,
                            score: newScore
                        };
                        document.querySelector("#choice_id_"+x).click();
                    };
                document.querySelector('div.question__question > p').innerHTML = "<div style='border:1px solid black'><h3>I am "+(Math.floor(likelyAnswer.score * 100))+"% sure.</h3><p>Their answer choice: <strong>"+likelyAnswer.theirAnswer+"</strong></p><p>Our answer: <strong>"+likelyAnswer.ourAnswer+"</strong></p>";
                };
            };
        };
    };

}



function matchQuestions(questionTodo, possibleAnswers){
    var rightAnswers = {};
    var questionInFile;
    var answers;
    var answerNum;
    var mostLikely = {
        score: 0.0,
        question: "who the fuck?"
    };
    var oldScore = 0;
    var newScore = 0;

    for (var key in all_qa) {
        if (all_qa.hasOwnProperty(key)) {
    
            questionInFile = all_qa[key].question;
            answers  = all_qa[key].answer;
            answerNum = answers.length;

            oldScore = JaroWrinker(questionInFile.trim(), questionTodo.trim());
            if(oldScore > newScore) {
                newScore = oldScore;
                var mostLikely = {
                    score: newScore,
                    question: questionInFile,
                    answer: answers
                };
            };
        };
    };
    return mostLikely;
};

 
